<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Book Review on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/tags/book-review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Book Review on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 04:07:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/tags/book-review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Vegetarian by Han Kang</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-vegetarian-by-han-kang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 04:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-vegetarian-by-han-kang/</guid>
      <description>Yeong-hye and her husband are ordinary people. He is an office worker with moderate ambitions and mild manners; she is an uninspired but dutiful wife. The acceptable flatline of their marriage is interrupted when Yeong-hye, seeking a more &amp;#8216;plant-like&amp;rsquo; existence, decides to become a vegetarian, prompted by grotesque recurring nightmares. In South Korea, where vegetarianism is almost unheard-of and societal mores are strictly obeyed, Yeong-hye&amp;rsquo;s decision is a shocking act of subversion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Vital Signs by Tessa McWatt</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-vital-signs-by-tessa-mcwatt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 10:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-vital-signs-by-tessa-mcwatt/</guid>
      <description>After thirty years of marriage, producing three now-grown children, Mike and Anna have settled into entrenched domesticity. She is skillful and poised and still beautiful, an instructor of English at the city college. He is a successful graphic artist on the verge of retirement, his awards and ambitions and accomplishments largely behind him. Though the couple’s erotic life has dimmed somewhat, he still considers her ravishing.
But their apparent balance is thrown asunder when Anna breaks the normal silence of their breakfast table with uncontrollable babble about hummingbirds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Frankenstein by Mary Shelley</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-frankenstein-by-mary-shelley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 06:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-frankenstein-by-mary-shelley/</guid>
      <description>To many readers, who have perhaps known Frankenstein only at second hand, the original may well come as a surprise. When Mary Shelley began it, she was only eighteen, though she was already Shelley&amp;rsquo;s mistress and Byron&amp;rsquo;s friend. In her preface she explains how she and Shelley spent part of a wet summer with Byron in Switzerland, amusing themselves by reading and writing ghost stories. Her contribution was Frankenstein, a story about a student of natural philosophy who learns the secret of imparting life to a creature constructed from bones he has collected in charnel-houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Nine Island by Jane Alison</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-nine-island-by-jane-alison/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 17:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-nine-island-by-jane-alison/</guid>
      <description>Nine Island is an intimate autobiographical novel, told by J, a woman who lives in a glass tower on one of Miami Beach’s lush Venetian Islands. After decades of disaster with men, she is trying to decide whether to withdraw forever from romantic love. Having just returned to Miami from a monthlong reunion with an old flame, “Sir Gold,” and a visit to her fragile mother, J begins translating Ovid’s magical stories about the transformations caused by Eros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Birthday of the World and Other Stories by Ursula K. Le Guin</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-birthday-of-the-world-and-other-stories-by-ursula-k-le-guin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-birthday-of-the-world-and-other-stories-by-ursula-k-le-guin/</guid>
      <description>For more than four decades, Ursula K. Le Guin has enthralled readers with her imagination, clarity, and moral vision. The recipient of numerous literary prizes, including the National Book Award, the Kafka Award, and five Hugo and five Nebula Awards, this renowned writer has, in each story and novel, created a provocative, ever-evolving universe filled with diverse worlds and rich characters reminiscent of our earthly selves.
Now, in The Birthday of the World, this gifted artist returns to these worlds in eight brilliant short works, including a never-before-published novella, each of which probes the essence of humanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Gamelife by Michael Clune</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-gamelife-by-michael-clune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-gamelife-by-michael-clune/</guid>
      <description>You have been awakened.
Floppy disk inserted, computer turned on, a whirring, and then this sentence, followed by a blinking cursor. So begins Suspended, the first computer game to obsess seven-year-old Michael, to worm into his head and change his sense of reality. Thirty years later he will write: &amp;ldquo;Computer games have taught me the things you can&amp;rsquo;t learn from people.&amp;rdquo;
Gamelife is the memoir of a childhood transformed by technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Reivew: Manga Classics – Emma by Stacy King</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-reivew-manga-classics-emma-by-stacy-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 21:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-reivew-manga-classics-emma-by-stacy-king/</guid>
      <description>Just in time for the 200th Anniversary, Manga Classics: Emma brings Jane Austen&amp;rsquo;s classic tale of youthful folly and romantic exuberance to a modern audience with this beautiful, new manga adaptation. The impulsive match-making of Emma Woodhouse delivers both humor and heartache through the gorgeous artwork of manga-ka Po Tse (Manga Classics: Pride and Prejudice). &amp;#8211; Manga Classics editions feature classic stories, faithfully adapted and illustrated in manga style, and available in both hardcover and softcover editions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Amity by Nasreen Pevjak</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-amity-by-nasreen-pevjak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-amity-by-nasreen-pevjak/</guid>
      <description>Amity provides a window to the wreckage caused by wars—the destruction and displacement that leave pain and life-long psychological disorders, here specifically within the contexts of Yugoslavia’s dissolution and Iran’s revolution.
Payvand, an Iranian refugee and activist, still plagued with nightmares, meets a Ragusa, a Yugoslavian refugee whose pockets are loaded with stones as she prepares to walk into the water and end her life, a life that has become intolerable since the loss of those most dear to her.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>