<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crochet on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/crochet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crochet on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 04:45:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/crochet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FO: Candy Print Alpine Nights Beanie</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-candy-print-alpine-nights-beanie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 04:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-candy-print-alpine-nights-beanie/</guid>
      <description>FO stands for &amp;ldquo;finished object.&amp;rdquo; It is a term used by knitters and crocheters.
 I recently finished a hat that my cousin asked me to make for her daughter. At first I wanted to knit a hat but I decided to crochet it instead. I looked through many different patterns and had trouble finding one that I liked the most. I settled on Alpine Nights because the pattern seemed not only simple but also very pretty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m a Little Behind</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/im-a-little-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/im-a-little-behind/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days ago I was behind on my granny squares for my temperature blanket. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know, temperature blankets consist of one square a day and each square represents the temperature of that day. Thankfully, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to catch up with temperature blankets! Even though I&amp;rsquo;m caught up with the squares, I still haven&amp;rsquo;t woven the ends in yet nor have I joined them. Eek!
Last week I was babysitting my little cousin and he was playing with my yarn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Steps Forward, One Step Back</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/two-steps-forward-one-step-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 03:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/two-steps-forward-one-step-back/</guid>
      <description>I finally finished one Bernat Blanket Stripes cake! I am going to move onto cake number two for my afghan ripple blanket. I don&amp;rsquo;t really know yet who this blanket will be for. My mom keeps asking me and I can&amp;rsquo;t make up my mind. I am pretty happy that I am making progress on this blanket. I might need three cakes for this though and not the two that I have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STASH Lounge Moving and Other Outings</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/stash-lounge-moving-and-other-outings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 03:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/stash-lounge-moving-and-other-outings/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday Yesterday opened up at their new location across the street. I dragged my brother along with me to the opening.
It was absolutely lovely! They had a DJ play some music in the background, a coffee bar, and a table of yummy sweets in the back. They even had door prizes, which I suspect I didn&amp;rsquo;t win anything from but that&amp;rsquo;s totally okay.
In terms of the space, it&amp;rsquo;s great!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Time Crocheting on a Road Trip</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/first-time-crocheting-on-a-road-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 15:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/first-time-crocheting-on-a-road-trip/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I went to Drumheller with the family. Up to this point I haven&amp;rsquo;t had a chance to go on a long road trip with my crochet. I started this ripple afghan a couple of days ago with Bernat Blanket Stripes yarn. This blanket is intended for my cousins&amp;rsquo;s newborn son. I guess he isn&amp;rsquo;t quite so newborn now but every baby could use a blanket regardless! I actually restarted this blanket once or twice but I finally got the hang of it while on this trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting a Nanodegree at Udacity</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/programming/starting-a-nanodegree-at-udacity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 18:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/programming/starting-a-nanodegree-at-udacity/</guid>
      <description>While I&amp;rsquo;m still looking for a job this summer (which is almost halfway over already&amp;#8230; Blah!) I took a cue from Y who started to work on some side projects and I decided to be a little more productive. Since I have a free month of Udacity from the GitHub Student Pack. Udacity is basically an online learning hub where you can take courses that are related to the tech field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #6: My Second Granny Square</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-6-my-second-granny-square/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 04:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-6-my-second-granny-square/</guid>
      <description>FO means &amp;ldquo;finished object&amp;rdquo; in crochet and knitter terms. So any completed project is a finished object!
 After making my first granny square, I quickly made my second granny square. Both were made from Loop &amp;amp; Threads yarn of the wool variety. I can&amp;rsquo;t remember the exact name of the yarn.
I am not quite sure about the colour choices but they were the colours I had on hand of the same yarn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winding Yarn Multitasking</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/winding-yarn-multitasking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 10:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/winding-yarn-multitasking/</guid>
      <description>Since I recently started making a temperature blanket. I bought a couple of skeins of yarn (Bernat Premium, they are so soft!) and decided to wind them into balls to make transporting them easier for when/if I&amp;rsquo;m on the go. Surprisingly, it takes a while for them to wind up. I thought it was a perfect opportunity to watch some TV shows while doing it.
I decided to finish up watching season 2 of Knights of Sidonia, an anime about a human space colony at war with alien-like creatures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Out in Pre-Stampede Rush</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/day-out-in-pre-stampede-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/day-out-in-pre-stampede-rush/</guid>
      <description>I went to the first pancake breakfast of the season with my family the other day. It was close to home which was a great bonus because my dad had the car for work. The breakfast wasn&amp;rsquo;t busy at all but maybe being fairly early was a factor. They only served pancakes and sausage patties but they were pretty good! There was also a Tim Hortons truck giving out free coffee and hot chocolate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canada 150 Temperature Blanket: First Colour Change</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/canada-150-temperature-blanket-first-colour-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 22:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/canada-150-temperature-blanket-first-colour-change/</guid>
      <description>A post shared by Edel Altares (@edelgraceme) on Jul 5, 2017 at 3:41pm PDT   Since the beginning of July, I&amp;rsquo;ve been recording the highs and lows of the daily temperature through granny squares. The middle colour represents the low of the day and the outer colour represents the high of the day. The first three days of July were roughly the same but the fourth was a little bit cooler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yarn Haul #8: Gina Brown’s First Visit</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-8-gina-browns-first-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-8-gina-browns-first-visit/</guid>
      <description>I went to visit another local yarn store called Gina Brown&amp;rsquo;s. I was in the area waiting to meet up with some friends and decided to pop in and check the place out. It&amp;rsquo;s way too convenient that this place is a ten minute walk away from a train station.
It&amp;rsquo;s a nice store. In the back there&amp;rsquo;s a big table available for classes and (I&amp;rsquo;m assuming) to just knit or crochet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yarn Haul #7: The Knitting Room First Visit</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-7-the-knitting-room-first-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 07:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-7-the-knitting-room-first-visit/</guid>
      <description>I have been going to the Brentwood Village Mall for the past couple of years now and I have never ever noticed this nice little yarn store before until I started up crochet. The Knitting Room is a small store located in a mall close to my university. I usually go to the mall when I&amp;rsquo;m itching to walk somewhere between classes. I decided to finally visit The Knitting Room for the first time and came away with some yarn!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hooked on Crochet Spring 2017 Swap</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/hooked-on-crochet-spring-2017-swap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 17:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/hooked-on-crochet-spring-2017-swap/</guid>
      <description>Hooked on Crochet is a Discord server that I am a part of. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what Discord is, it is essentially a chat client for gamers. You can create your own &amp;ldquo;servers&amp;rdquo; or chat rooms for dedicated topics. Hooked on Crochet is (obviously) a group of crocheters. They organized a yarn swap last spring which I took a part of.
My gifter got me a set of hand dyed Alpaca yarn, a llama stitch marker, and a pattern for a unicorn amigurumi!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #5: My First Granny Square</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-5-my-first-granny-square/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 18:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-5-my-first-granny-square/</guid>
      <description>My previous FO was part of the March National Crochet Month and this one is no different. Except this event is a charity run. This square will be going to a charity to be part of a blanket! Different squares from different people will all be sewn together. I think it&amp;rsquo;s a cool joint effort!

It took me a swatch to get the hang of making a granny square. Thankfully the process is straightforward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #4: NatCroMo2017 Mystery Crochet Along</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-4-natcromo2017-mystery-crochet-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 08:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-4-natcromo2017-mystery-crochet-along/</guid>
      <description>March is National Crochet Month. A group on Ravelry holds a series of events during the month to celebrate. One of these events is a mystery crochet along! Basically, the finished product is a mystery and parts of the pattern is slowly released throughout the month.
There were times I fell a little behind the clues but I managed to finish it off! Honestly, I find it a little bit derpy but that&amp;rsquo;s part of it&amp;rsquo;s charm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crochet Haul #6: Blanket Mania</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-6-blanket-mania/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-6-blanket-mania/</guid>
      <description>I decided to make a baby blanket for my cousin who is due in June. I bought a ton of Bernat Blanket skeins for this project. There is a big sale going on at Michael&amp;rsquo;s so I kept getting discount after discount. Which is good because I could never imagine buying this many skeins of Bernat Blanket at full price. I may have actually bought too many. I did buy one skein at Walmart though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #3: Dot’s Little Ditty Bag – Perpetually Loading</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-3-dots-little-ditty-bag-perpetually-loading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 19:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-3-dots-little-ditty-bag-perpetually-loading/</guid>
      <description>I made this little bag mostly while playing the MMO Blade &amp;amp; Soul, hence the title &amp;ldquo;Perpetually Loading.&amp;rdquo; My computer is a bit of a toaster so I managed to get a lot of crocheting done while on the loading screen. Sometimes my game would crash on the loading screen and that would mean even more crocheting for me! Unfortunately, this worked out to the disadvantage of my SO who I was playing with at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crochet Haul #5: First Michael’s Trip</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-5-first-michaels-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 12:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-5-first-michaels-trip/</guid>
      <description>I recently found out that there was a Michael&amp;rsquo;s near my workplace. Rookie mistake. After work, I walked over to the store. It&amp;rsquo;s a 20 minute walk in an area with absolutely no sidewalks. The snow hindered me a little bit but not enough to make me turn away!
Okay, this is actually my second Michael&amp;rsquo;s yarn trip but the first time, I didn&amp;rsquo;t buy a single thing. I just went to check out the place and see the different kinds of brands they had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #2: Easy and Thin Dishcloth</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-2-easy-and-thin-dishcloth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 12:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-2-easy-and-thin-dishcloth/</guid>
      <description>This next dishcloth I made was a simple green dishcloth with single crochets. What initially drew me to the pattern was that the texture of the dishcloth was very pretty. I was surprised to know that the variance in texture was simple due to changing which loop you inserted the hook in! While it isn&amp;rsquo;t completely perfect, by the time I finished this I felt a lot more confident in my single crochets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crochet Haul #4: HiKoo Simplicity</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-4-hikoo-simplicity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-4-hikoo-simplicity/</guid>
      <description>I made a post about participating in Crochet Along Together (CAT) to make a three colour cowl and the yarn I ordered for the project finally arrived! It was good timing too because the event started the next day. I was getting a little worried that it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t arrive in time.
Despite the discount I got on the yarn due specifically to the CAT (the CAT was sponsored by this brand, I think), it was kind of pricey for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crochet Haul #3: Vanna’s Choice in Silver Grey Yarn</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-3-vannas-choice-in-silver-grey-yarn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 21:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-3-vannas-choice-in-silver-grey-yarn/</guid>
      <description>When I bought my crochet hook set, I needed to buy an additional $15 worth of products so I could get free shipping. It saved me around five dollars and there was no point in getting hooks without any yarn.
Unfortunately, they shipped it separate from the hooks but I had bought yarn from Walmart in the meantime while waiting for my things to arrive.
So here is the skein of yarn I got from Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Crochet Month 2017: Mystery Crochet Along Clues 1 &amp; 2</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/national-crochet-month-2017-mystery-crochet-along-clues-1-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 20:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/national-crochet-month-2017-mystery-crochet-along-clues-1-2/</guid>
      <description>The group []() on Ravelry are holding an MCAL (Mystery Crochet Along) which I am taking part of. The project is an amigurumi. I have never made an amigurumi before and this will be my first! It will be interesting seeing that I have no idea what the finished project will look like. These are the first two clues finished. I still need to start clue 3 and 4, I&amp;rsquo;m a little behind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #1: Corchet Guru Dishcloth</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-1-corchet-guru-dishcloth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 21:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-1-corchet-guru-dishcloth/</guid>
      <description>On February 26 I finished my very first project! It&amp;rsquo;s only a simple dishcloth as I&amp;rsquo;m just starting out. I know the colours are kind of garish but I never thought I&amp;rsquo;d be using them together until I actually started working on it. I can see some of the mistakes I made, and there are many, but I am extremely happy with how it turned out and I had a lot of fun making it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planned Projects for March 2017</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/planned-projects-for-march-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/planned-projects-for-march-2017/</guid>
      <description>As you may have noticed, I recently took up learning how to crochet. Since March is National Crochet Month, &amp;nbsp;I decided to take part in some of the activities that are being held at Ravelry.
MCAL (Mystery Crochet Along)
This is an event that reveals the pattern slowly, clue by clue. The only hint is that it&amp;rsquo;s an anigurumi made out of three colours. This will be my first amigurumi so I&amp;rsquo;m quite excited but also anxious that it won&amp;rsquo;t turn out well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crochet Haul #2: Cheap Crochet Set</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-2-cheap-crochet-set/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-2-cheap-crochet-set/</guid>
      <description>Since I&amp;rsquo;m just starting out with crocheting, I bought a somewhat cheap crochet set on Amazon. I&amp;rsquo;m hesitant to buy high end luxury tools if I&amp;rsquo;m not even sure I want to continue crocheting. I do think it would be a worthy hobby to take part in!
The case itself is seriously cute. The brand seems to be Merrywindix but I can&amp;rsquo;t quite tell. It&amp;rsquo;s a lot smaller than I expected which is great, that means it&amp;rsquo;s extremely portable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crochet Along Together #1: Easy as 1-2-3 Cowl (Part 1)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-along-together-1-easy-as-1-2-3-cowl-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-along-together-1-easy-as-1-2-3-cowl-part-1/</guid>
      <description>The fine folks at Skacel Knitting are hosting a series they call &amp;ldquo;Crochet Along Together&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;CAT&amp;rdquo; for short. They post videos throughout the month to walk you through the project. A draw is also held after the project is finished.
March CAT
This is their very first installment and is geared towards (but not limited to) beginners to crochet. The project for this months is the Easy As 1-2-3 Cowl which is a three colour cowl.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>