<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 04:07:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Vegetarian by Han Kang</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-vegetarian-by-han-kang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 04:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-vegetarian-by-han-kang/</guid>
      <description>Yeong-hye and her husband are ordinary people. He is an office worker with moderate ambitions and mild manners; she is an uninspired but dutiful wife. The acceptable flatline of their marriage is interrupted when Yeong-hye, seeking a more &amp;#8216;plant-like&amp;rsquo; existence, decides to become a vegetarian, prompted by grotesque recurring nightmares. In South Korea, where vegetarianism is almost unheard-of and societal mores are strictly obeyed, Yeong-hye&amp;rsquo;s decision is a shocking act of subversion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: God in Pink by Hasan Namir</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-god-in-pink-by-hasan-namir/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 22:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-god-in-pink-by-hasan-namir/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Topics of sexuality, religion, and spoilers for the book is mentioned in this blog post.
 A revelatory novel about being queer and Muslim, set in war-torn Iraq in 2003. Ramy is a young gay Iraqi struggling to find a balance between his sexuality, religion, and culture. Ammar is a sheikh whose guidance Ramy seeks, and whose tolerance is tested by his belief in the teachings of the Qur&amp;rsquo;an. Full of quiet moments of beauty and raw depictions of violence, God in Pink poignantly captures the anguish and the fortitude of Islamic life in Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #21</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-21/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Name a book that changed your life.
 Busting out the big questions. This is a hard one to answer. I think that I&amp;rsquo;m still trying to find it. I have my favourite books but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure of their impact on my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #20</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 07:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-20/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 If you are at a really good point in a book and the phone rings or the door bell rings, do you stop reading or let the phone or door bell go unanswered?
 Honestly, I would get up and check them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Vital Signs by Tessa McWatt</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-vital-signs-by-tessa-mcwatt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 10:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-vital-signs-by-tessa-mcwatt/</guid>
      <description>After thirty years of marriage, producing three now-grown children, Mike and Anna have settled into entrenched domesticity. She is skillful and poised and still beautiful, an instructor of English at the city college. He is a successful graphic artist on the verge of retirement, his awards and ambitions and accomplishments largely behind him. Though the couple’s erotic life has dimmed somewhat, he still considers her ravishing.
But their apparent balance is thrown asunder when Anna breaks the normal silence of their breakfast table with uncontrollable babble about hummingbirds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #19</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 07:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-19/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How do you organize your blog in terms of what is in your side bar? Do you have categories and defined sections in your side bar?
 At the moment, my side bar is laid out by links to my favourite bloggers, categories, monthly archives, and recent comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Frankenstein by Mary Shelley</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-frankenstein-by-mary-shelley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 06:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-frankenstein-by-mary-shelley/</guid>
      <description>To many readers, who have perhaps known Frankenstein only at second hand, the original may well come as a surprise. When Mary Shelley began it, she was only eighteen, though she was already Shelley&amp;rsquo;s mistress and Byron&amp;rsquo;s friend. In her preface she explains how she and Shelley spent part of a wet summer with Byron in Switzerland, amusing themselves by reading and writing ghost stories. Her contribution was Frankenstein, a story about a student of natural philosophy who learns the secret of imparting life to a creature constructed from bones he has collected in charnel-houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #18</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 07:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-18/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 If you could have lunch with any living authors and/or book bloggers, who would you choose and why?
 Oh man, the living restriction is a tough one. If language wasn&amp;rsquo;t a barrier, I would definitely have lunch with Haruki Murakami.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Nine Island by Jane Alison</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-nine-island-by-jane-alison/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 17:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-nine-island-by-jane-alison/</guid>
      <description>Nine Island is an intimate autobiographical novel, told by J, a woman who lives in a glass tower on one of Miami Beach’s lush Venetian Islands. After decades of disaster with men, she is trying to decide whether to withdraw forever from romantic love. Having just returned to Miami from a monthlong reunion with an old flame, “Sir Gold,” and a visit to her fragile mother, J begins translating Ovid’s magical stories about the transformations caused by Eros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #17</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 07:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-17/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do your bookshelves have books ONLY or do you also have bookish items on the shelves?
 I have books, bookish items, and non-bookish items on my shelves. Actually my shelves are in a pretty sorry state. There is a lot of clutter on them and they&amp;rsquo;re usually my go to place to put things when I have no idea where to put them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #15</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hope-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hope-15/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 When you feature a book in your posts, do you include a book cover?
 I definitely try my best to do so. It seems a little weird to write a blog post about a book without featuring the cover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #14</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-14/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 If you could meet one author, dead or alive, who would it be? Submitted by Kristin @ Lukten av Trykksverte
 I am in love with the Brontë sisters. Their lives intrigue me a great deal and the sense of mystery surrounding them is too much for me to take at times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Birthday of the World and Other Stories by Ursula K. Le Guin</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-birthday-of-the-world-and-other-stories-by-ursula-k-le-guin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-birthday-of-the-world-and-other-stories-by-ursula-k-le-guin/</guid>
      <description>For more than four decades, Ursula K. Le Guin has enthralled readers with her imagination, clarity, and moral vision. The recipient of numerous literary prizes, including the National Book Award, the Kafka Award, and five Hugo and five Nebula Awards, this renowned writer has, in each story and novel, created a provocative, ever-evolving universe filled with diverse worlds and rich characters reminiscent of our earthly selves.
Now, in The Birthday of the World, this gifted artist returns to these worlds in eight brilliant short works, including a never-before-published novella, each of which probes the essence of humanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #13</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 08:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-13/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you visit every listed blog in the linky list when you are participating in a meme? Submitted by Elizabeth @ Silver&amp;rsquo;s Reviews
 I try to! But I don&amp;rsquo;t always manage to do so. I usually do my blog hopping on the train to/from work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Gamelife by Michael Clune</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-gamelife-by-michael-clune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-gamelife-by-michael-clune/</guid>
      <description>You have been awakened.
Floppy disk inserted, computer turned on, a whirring, and then this sentence, followed by a blinking cursor. So begins Suspended, the first computer game to obsess seven-year-old Michael, to worm into his head and change his sense of reality. Thirty years later he will write: &amp;ldquo;Computer games have taught me the things you can&amp;rsquo;t learn from people.&amp;rdquo;
Gamelife is the memoir of a childhood transformed by technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #12</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 06:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-12/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How do you handle negative comments left on your blog? Submitted by Maria @ A Night&amp;rsquo;s Dream of Books
 Thankfully, I haven&amp;rsquo;t encountered this problem before. 🙂 And if I have, obviously I must have handled it well because it didn&amp;rsquo;t make a lasting impression on me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Reivew: Manga Classics – Emma by Stacy King</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-reivew-manga-classics-emma-by-stacy-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 21:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-reivew-manga-classics-emma-by-stacy-king/</guid>
      <description>Just in time for the 200th Anniversary, Manga Classics: Emma brings Jane Austen&amp;rsquo;s classic tale of youthful folly and romantic exuberance to a modern audience with this beautiful, new manga adaptation. The impulsive match-making of Emma Woodhouse delivers both humor and heartache through the gorgeous artwork of manga-ka Po Tse (Manga Classics: Pride and Prejudice). &amp;#8211; Manga Classics editions feature classic stories, faithfully adapted and illustrated in manga style, and available in both hardcover and softcover editions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #11</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 06:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-11/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you read a lot of diverse or own voices books? Why or why not? Submitted by Kitty @ Vicarious Bookworm
 Hmm&amp;#8230; I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what this question means so I&amp;rsquo;m going to take a stab at it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Amity by Nasreen Pevjak</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-amity-by-nasreen-pevjak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-amity-by-nasreen-pevjak/</guid>
      <description>Amity provides a window to the wreckage caused by wars—the destruction and displacement that leave pain and life-long psychological disorders, here specifically within the contexts of Yugoslavia’s dissolution and Iran’s revolution.
Payvand, an Iranian refugee and activist, still plagued with nightmares, meets a Ragusa, a Yugoslavian refugee whose pockets are loaded with stones as she prepares to walk into the water and end her life, a life that has become intolerable since the loss of those most dear to her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #10</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-10/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How far in advance do you read the books you have scheduled for review?
 I don&amp;rsquo;t read books &amp;ldquo;ahead of time.&amp;rdquo; I just read books with no schedule in mind and review them as I go. I guess this question is geared towards the more veteran book bloggers who recieve copies of books to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #9</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 08:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-9/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 When you start reading a novel, do you prefer to be plunged right into the action, or do you prefer a slower, more descriptive introduction to the plot and characters? Submitted by Maria @ [
 
Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #8</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-8/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How do you feel about books with multiple narrators? Submitted by Eli @ The Book Supplier
 I definitely don&amp;rsquo;t mind them nor do I have a preference towards them. My opinion isn&amp;rsquo;t fresh as I haven&amp;rsquo;t read a book with multiple narrators in a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #7 (02/17-02/23)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-7-0217-0223/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 13:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-7-0217-0223/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Can you read and watch TV or listen to the radio at the same time? Submitted by Elizabeth @ [Silver&amp;rsquo;s Reviews]()
 Nope! Unless we&amp;rsquo;re talking about dry, academic textbooks. I can read the words but nothing will go into my head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it Possible to Read Too Much?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/is-it-possible-to-read-too-much/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 02:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/is-it-possible-to-read-too-much/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m in a weird place where I&amp;rsquo;m reading a lot but I&amp;rsquo;m unsure if I&amp;rsquo;m feeling depressed because I&amp;rsquo;m reading too much or I&amp;rsquo;m reading too much because I&amp;rsquo;m feeling depressed.
I&amp;rsquo;ve always thought of books as an escape. That sounds a little too negative but I enjoy experiencing a story that I would probably never experience myself. Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve gravitated to historical fiction because it&amp;rsquo;s just so different and unknown territory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #6 (02/10-02/16)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-6-0210-0216/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 20:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-6-0210-0216/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 What is your favorite Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day read? Submitted by Kristin @ Lukten av Trykksverte
 Is it okay for me to say that I don&amp;rsquo;t have any&amp;#8230;? I don&amp;rsquo;t really read anything specifically for Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day. I also don&amp;rsquo;t recall any Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day themed books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #5 (02/03-02/09)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-5-0203-0209/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 20:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-5-0203-0209/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Read or Clean? Read or Bake? Read or Make Dinner? What would be your choice? Submitted by Elizabeth @ Silver&amp;rsquo;s Reviews
 There are quite a lot of questions for today!
 Read or Clean? If I play my cards right, both!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #4 (01/27-02/02/2017)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-4-0127-02022017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-4-0127-02022017/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How many books have you statted but just couldn&amp;rsquo;t finish? Submitted by Elizabeth @ Silver&amp;rsquo;s Reviews
 How many? As in, a specific number? Too many to count. Actually, that&amp;rsquo;s not accurate. I don&amp;rsquo;t really know the answer to that question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #3 (01/20-01/26/2017)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-3-0120-01262017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-3-0120-01262017/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 What was the one time you thought the movie was better than the book? Submitted by Tomi @ A Bookworm&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Life
 Okay, this is a really tough one. I am sure I have watched plenty of book movies but I haven&amp;rsquo;t always read the book counterpart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Read: Mary and The Wrongs of Woman by Mary Wollstonecraft</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/i-read-mary-and-the-wrongs-of-woman-by-mary-wollstonecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 03:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/i-read-mary-and-the-wrongs-of-woman-by-mary-wollstonecraft/</guid>
      <description>I recently finished reading Mary and The Wrongs of Woman by Mary Wollstonecraft. I received this book from a friend of my mothers. I actually received multiple books from my mother&amp;rsquo;s friend, many of them classics such as Villette by Charlotte Bronte, Emma by Jane Austen, Frankenstein by Mary Shelly (who is, by the way, the daughter of Mary Wollstonecraft), etc. I managed to find many books that I enjoyed from her gift.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favourite Book of 2016</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/my-favourite-book-of-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 02:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/my-favourite-book-of-2016/</guid>
      <description>This is very long overdue but I was blog hopping and came across The Daily Prophecy ran by Mel. Her latest post was a quick survey of all the books she read in 2016. At the end of her post, she posed the question:
 What is the best book you read in 2016?
 This is a very tough question for me to answer. I read a couple of very good books this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #2 (01/13-01/19/2017)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-2-0113-01192017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-2-0113-01192017/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Is everyday a reading day for you? Submitted by Elizabeth @ Silver&amp;rsquo;s Reviews
 I&amp;rsquo;m trying to make it a habit of reading everyday. Realistically though, I only really read during the work week. Those days I specifically block out times for myself dedicated for reading: on the way to and from work (since I take public transportation).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #1 (01/06-01/12/2017)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Where&amp;rsquo;s your favourite place to read? Submitted by Ronyell @ Rabbit Ears Book Blog
 I will be honest&amp;#8230; I don&amp;rsquo;t think I have a favourite place, as long as I&amp;rsquo;m reading. In terms of places where I usually read is on the bus or when I&amp;rsquo;m eating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to Work…</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/back-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 03:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/back-to-work/</guid>
      <description>The holidays are officially over, for I went back to work today. It was a bit of a slow day. I got my internship extended, however they basically treated me as a new hire since my contract ended in December. So I&amp;rsquo;m starting from scratch, essentially. I had no laptop, no e-mail, no account to login into any computer connected to the company&amp;rsquo;s network&amp;#8230; Kinda rough.
However, I did manage to do some small tasks that didn&amp;rsquo;t require the use of a computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 Reading Resolutions</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/2017-reading-resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 05:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/2017-reading-resolutions/</guid>
      <description>This year I told myself I would read at least 25 books. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem like a lot but when you consider my reading history the past couple of years, that&amp;rsquo;s a big number.
 2015: 7 books + 3 graphic novels = 10 books 2014: 19 books + 20 graphic novels = 39 books 2013: 40 books + 30 graphic novels = 74 books 2012: 18 books  As you can see, not great numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At the Library #13</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/at-the-library-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 04:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/at-the-library-13/</guid>
      <description>I recently made a trip to the library. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I managed to grab.
Buried in Books: A Reader&amp;rsquo;s Anthology by Julie Rugg
There are quite a lot of books on my to-read list that I don&amp;rsquo;t recall exactly why they&amp;rsquo;re on the list. But I trust myself if a book is on the list. I actually culled off the more obvious ones but the ones that stayed are ones that really interest me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Just Culled My Book Wish List</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/i-just-culled-my-book-wish-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 02:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/i-just-culled-my-book-wish-list/</guid>
      <description>On Goodreads, my &amp;ldquo;want-to-own&amp;rdquo; shelf used to have 127 books in it. Now it has five.
Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been bit by the konmari bug. I&amp;rsquo;ve konmari&amp;rsquo;d my wardrobe and my books so far. I&amp;rsquo;m still stuck on the books. I decided it would be fitting to prevent my book collection from growing back to it&amp;rsquo;s ridiculous size and get rid of anything that doesn&amp;rsquo;t spark joy on my book wish list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At the Library #12</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/at-the-library-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 04:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/at-the-library-12/</guid>
      <description>I recently resolved not to take out any library books unless they were on my to read list. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I took out on my latest trip to the library!
Speak by Laurie Halse Anderson
I don&amp;rsquo;t remember why or how this book got onto my to read list but I know that it&amp;rsquo;s been on the list for quite a while. I was glad to see the book sitting on the shelf since I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading: The Secret Diaries of Charlotte Brontë</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/reading-the-secret-diaries-of-charlotte-bronte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 13:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/reading-the-secret-diaries-of-charlotte-bronte/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m extremely fond of Charlotte Brontë. Villette is easily my favourite novel and I hold it very close to my heart. A couple week ago I finally got around to reading Jane Eyre and it did not disappoint. The other members of the Brontë family are not to be overlooked either. I enjoyed Emily&amp;rsquo;s Wuthering Heights and all of Anne&amp;rsquo;s books are in my to read list. So when I stumbled upon The Secret Diaries of Charlotte Brontë by Syrie James in the library, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist picking it up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100 Books Every Man Should Read</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/100-books-every-man-should-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 01:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/100-books-every-man-should-read/</guid>
      <description>The Art of Manliness put out this list of books. I am not a man but we&amp;rsquo;ll see how I do with this list. Turns I&amp;rsquo;ve only read 8% of this list. Out of the books I want to read from this list, I&amp;rsquo;ve read 24%. Not any better, but hey. I&amp;rsquo;m really trying to cull the books I want to read though. I will never be able to read everything I want to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comics Aren’t Just Kids Stuff!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/comics-arent-just-kids-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 01:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/comics-arent-just-kids-stuff/</guid>
      <description>I initially started writing this post in 2012. I&amp;rsquo;ve been going through and cleaning out my drafts and decided this one was worthy of continuing and actually publishing.
Comics are usually written off as being childish or something only nerds can enjoy. But, I&amp;rsquo;m not here to argue whether comics are legitimate literature or not. I&amp;rsquo;m here to point out some of my favourite web comics. I don&amp;rsquo;t know where it started but I got bored one day and eventually ended up on a web comics site.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>