<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 01:42:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Guitar: Week 1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/music/learning-the-guitar-week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 01:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/music/learning-the-guitar-week-1/</guid>
      <description>I have been following Justin Guitar&amp;#8216;s lesson plans for learning the guitar.
This week I went through the first 15 beginner&amp;rsquo;s course lessons, BC-101 to BC-115. I learned the basics of choosing a guitar, posture, etc. In terms of actually playing, I learned the D chord, A chord, and E chord. The first two chords were incredibly &amp;ldquo;easy.&amp;rdquo; The chord that really stumped me was the E chord. I could not press down on the strings hard enough so that it didn&amp;rsquo;t sound muted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Listened To: Electra Heart by Marina and the Diamonds</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/music/i-listened-to-electra-heart-by-marina-and-the-diamonds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/music/i-listened-to-electra-heart-by-marina-and-the-diamonds/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Lyrics relating to suicide is mentioned in this post.
Another disclaimer: I&amp;rsquo;m not good at writing reviews but I do like expressing my opinions. This is in no way a professional review but rather how I personally feel about this album.
I know Marina and the Diamonds&amp;rsquo; album Electra Heart is one of her personally least favourite works but I like it a lot. Many people think Electra Heart represents an alter-ego but it&amp;rsquo;s rather a personality that Marina holds in disdain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bought Some New Music!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/bought-some-new-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 03:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/bought-some-new-music/</guid>
      <description>Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Spotify a lot. I only ever use it when I&amp;rsquo;m at my computer. When I&amp;rsquo;m on the go, I turn to my trusty iPod classic. Since I use the free version of Spotify (now that I have a job, I can&amp;rsquo;t say that I&amp;rsquo;m a broke college student anymore but I can say that I&amp;rsquo;m still cheap), being able to choose what I listen to is a must and Spotify mobile doesn&amp;rsquo;t have that ability.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>