<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Networking on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/networking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Networking on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 02:36:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/networking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>TIL: IGMP</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/networking/til-igmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 02:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/networking/til-igmp/</guid>
      <description>Today I learned about IGMP, which stands for Internet Group Message Protocol. There are three different ways packets are sent out to other devices. There&amp;rsquo;s unicast, which just sends a packet to one specific device. Then there&amp;rsquo;s broadcast, which sends packets to all the devices that is in the network. Lastly, there&amp;rsquo;s multicast. Multicast sends packets to more than one device but not all the devices.
If a device wants to be part of a multicast group, it sends out an IGMP packet, or more specifically, an IGMP join packet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TIL: Adding Policies in Cisco Firewalls</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/networking/til-adding-policies-in-cisco-firewalls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 05:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/networking/til-adding-policies-in-cisco-firewalls/</guid>
      <description>Identify traffic with an access-list
access-list acl-name permit ip source destination dscp dscp-value Apply the access-list with the dscp value to an interfact
class-map match-all interface match ip dscp dscp-value Apply the policy
policy-map map-name class class-name [bandwidth bandwidth-value] [priority priority-level] set ip dscp dscp-value Today at work I was going over firewalls. We want to check the configuration of the firewalls and compare them to our QoS standards. I&amp;rsquo;m not too familiar with how policies and QoS are implemented on Cisco devices so it was pretty interesting to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>