<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crafts on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/crafts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crafts on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 11:05:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/crafts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Yarn Winding</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/yarn-winding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 11:05:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/yarn-winding/</guid>
      <description>My brother got me a yarn winder for my birthday last week and yesterday I spent the afternoon winding some yarn while watching Medici: Masters of Florence on Netflix.
  Yarn that has been winded    I just finished a block week course (a week long course ) on history of early modern Europe and I was bit by the Rrenaissance bug. Historial fiction is one of my favourite genres across multiple media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WIP Wednesday: Outline Ribbed Scarf</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/wip-wednesday-outline-ribbed-scarf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/wip-wednesday-outline-ribbed-scarf/</guid>
      <description>In my last post I talked about making my boyfriend a scarf. I started it yesterday after showing him a couple of sample swatches. Out of all the scarves I showed him, he liked this one of a crochet Outline Ribbed Scarf. It&amp;rsquo;s a rather simple scarf which is nice because it&amp;rsquo;ll work up quickly. Hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll finish the scarf by his birthday.
Here are some pictures of the test swatches I made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productive Distractions</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/productive-distractions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 19:06:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/productive-distractions/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s my boyfriend&amp;rsquo;s birthday coming up soon. I wanted to make him a knitted or a crocheted item because I need something to keep my hands busy. Plus aren&amp;rsquo;t handmade things the sweetest thing you could get as a present??
On some level, I know he&amp;rsquo;s a little picky about what kind of things he would like to wear. To avoid spending a ton of time working on something that he might not ever wear, I sent him a couple links to patterns of scarves and toques.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>