<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Fo on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/tags/fo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fo on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 04:45:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/tags/fo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>FO: Candy Print Alpine Nights Beanie</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-candy-print-alpine-nights-beanie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 04:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-candy-print-alpine-nights-beanie/</guid>
      <description>FO stands for &amp;ldquo;finished object.&amp;rdquo; It is a term used by knitters and crocheters.
 I recently finished a hat that my cousin asked me to make for her daughter. At first I wanted to knit a hat but I decided to crochet it instead. I looked through many different patterns and had trouble finding one that I liked the most. I settled on Alpine Nights because the pattern seemed not only simple but also very pretty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #5: My First Granny Square</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-5-my-first-granny-square/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 18:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-5-my-first-granny-square/</guid>
      <description>My previous FO was part of the March National Crochet Month and this one is no different. Except this event is a charity run. This square will be going to a charity to be part of a blanket! Different squares from different people will all be sewn together. I think it&amp;rsquo;s a cool joint effort!

It took me a swatch to get the hang of making a granny square. Thankfully the process is straightforward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #4: NatCroMo2017 Mystery Crochet Along</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-4-natcromo2017-mystery-crochet-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 08:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-4-natcromo2017-mystery-crochet-along/</guid>
      <description>March is National Crochet Month. A group on Ravelry holds a series of events during the month to celebrate. One of these events is a mystery crochet along! Basically, the finished product is a mystery and parts of the pattern is slowly released throughout the month.
There were times I fell a little behind the clues but I managed to finish it off! Honestly, I find it a little bit derpy but that&amp;rsquo;s part of it&amp;rsquo;s charm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #3: Dot’s Little Ditty Bag – Perpetually Loading</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-3-dots-little-ditty-bag-perpetually-loading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 19:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-3-dots-little-ditty-bag-perpetually-loading/</guid>
      <description>I made this little bag mostly while playing the MMO Blade &amp;amp; Soul, hence the title &amp;ldquo;Perpetually Loading.&amp;rdquo; My computer is a bit of a toaster so I managed to get a lot of crocheting done while on the loading screen. Sometimes my game would crash on the loading screen and that would mean even more crocheting for me! Unfortunately, this worked out to the disadvantage of my SO who I was playing with at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #2: Easy and Thin Dishcloth</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-2-easy-and-thin-dishcloth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 12:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-2-easy-and-thin-dishcloth/</guid>
      <description>This next dishcloth I made was a simple green dishcloth with single crochets. What initially drew me to the pattern was that the texture of the dishcloth was very pretty. I was surprised to know that the variance in texture was simple due to changing which loop you inserted the hook in! While it isn&amp;rsquo;t completely perfect, by the time I finished this I felt a lot more confident in my single crochets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #1: Corchet Guru Dishcloth</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-1-corchet-guru-dishcloth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 21:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-1-corchet-guru-dishcloth/</guid>
      <description>On February 26 I finished my very first project! It&amp;rsquo;s only a simple dishcloth as I&amp;rsquo;m just starting out. I know the colours are kind of garish but I never thought I&amp;rsquo;d be using them together until I actually started working on it. I can see some of the mistakes I made, and there are many, but I am extremely happy with how it turned out and I had a lot of fun making it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>