<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 11:05:12 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Yarn Winding</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/yarn-winding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 11:05:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/yarn-winding/</guid>
      <description>My brother got me a yarn winder for my birthday last week and yesterday I spent the afternoon winding some yarn while watching Medici: Masters of Florence on Netflix.
  Yarn that has been winded    I just finished a block week course (a week long course ) on history of early modern Europe and I was bit by the Rrenaissance bug. Historial fiction is one of my favourite genres across multiple media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uber Frugal Month January 2018 Day 2</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/uber-frugal-month-january-2018-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 22:44:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/uber-frugal-month-january-2018-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s mantra: When you&amp;rsquo;re working towards a goal, frugality isn&amp;rsquo;t about what you&amp;rsquo;re giving up, it&amp;rsquo;s about what you&amp;rsquo;re going to gain.
Today&amp;rsquo;s action: Write your long-term goal on a piece of paper and put it in your wallet.
Today&amp;rsquo;s reading: How I Figured Out What I Want To Do With My Life (And How You Can Too!)
The Homework The Dream Bio My Actual Bio
I was born in Calgary, Alberta, Canada to two Filipino immigrant parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Block Week</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/block-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 20:03:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/block-week/</guid>
      <description>I went back to school today. It&amp;rsquo;s a little weird to be back at school but also familiar. This semester is going to be a light one. I&amp;rsquo;m only taking two courses. One course is only five days long. So essentially I just have one course throughout the semester!
The block week course I&amp;rsquo;m taking right now is just a history course but it&amp;rsquo;s really interesting. I&amp;rsquo;ve always found history fascinating but I was never great at being tested on or writing about history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uber Frugal Month January 2018: Day 1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/uber-frugal-month-january-2018-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/uber-frugal-month-january-2018-day-1/</guid>
      <description>This is a month-long challenge held over at Frugalwoods. Feel free to join whenever you can!
Today&amp;rsquo;s Mantra: Anything in life that’s worth doing takes effort.
Today&amp;rsquo;s Action: Write down why you’re participating in the Uber and answers to
The Homework Step 1: Establish your goals Why are you participating in this challenge?
I want to build good spending habits for when I move out. I currently still live with my parents and admittedly am still quite spoiled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 2017</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-2017/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR/Highlights
I didn&amp;rsquo;t accomplish as much as I would have liked this year. However, this year was extremely eventful.
 Finished my internship and saved a lot of #MovingOut money Started and finished self-esteem group therapy Went to my first hackathon at Hack the North in Waterloo, Ontario Attended both the Calgary Expo and Calgary Expo Holiday Market Was a little more social this year Ate a lot of good food (AKA went to a ton of restaurants and pubs) Started crocheting and knitting  It&amp;rsquo;s been a wild year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WIP Wednesday: Outline Ribbed Scarf</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/wip-wednesday-outline-ribbed-scarf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/wip-wednesday-outline-ribbed-scarf/</guid>
      <description>In my last post I talked about making my boyfriend a scarf. I started it yesterday after showing him a couple of sample swatches. Out of all the scarves I showed him, he liked this one of a crochet Outline Ribbed Scarf. It&amp;rsquo;s a rather simple scarf which is nice because it&amp;rsquo;ll work up quickly. Hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll finish the scarf by his birthday.
Here are some pictures of the test swatches I made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productive Distractions</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/productive-distractions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 19:06:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/productive-distractions/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s my boyfriend&amp;rsquo;s birthday coming up soon. I wanted to make him a knitted or a crocheted item because I need something to keep my hands busy. Plus aren&amp;rsquo;t handmade things the sweetest thing you could get as a present??
On some level, I know he&amp;rsquo;s a little picky about what kind of things he would like to wear. To avoid spending a ton of time working on something that he might not ever wear, I sent him a couple links to patterns of scarves and toques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World (Hugo)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/hello-world-i-mean-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 20:59:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/hello-world-i-mean-hugo/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been tinkering with Hugo lately. A couple of weeks ago, I exported my old Wordpress blog into Hugo. While I am happy with the results, it&amp;rsquo;s taking me a bit of time to go through each of my posts (of which there are hundreds of) and update the metadata. I&amp;rsquo;m quite tempted to leave it as is but I enjoy consistency.
So here I am. A new portfolio. A technically new site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forever Tinkering with My Productivity System</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/forever-tinkering-with-my-productivity-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 23:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/forever-tinkering-with-my-productivity-system/</guid>
      <description>I follow the blog baty.net in which Jack Baty continuously finds new tools and new ways to improve his productivity. While I usually scoff at people who are always changing things up, I will admit that I am the exact same way. It would be great to just stick to something tried and true and never have to think about changing but there is just so much out there that it&amp;rsquo;s hard for me to resist the temptation to not try everything I can see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO: Candy Print Alpine Nights Beanie</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-candy-print-alpine-nights-beanie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 04:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-candy-print-alpine-nights-beanie/</guid>
      <description>FO stands for &amp;ldquo;finished object.&amp;rdquo; It is a term used by knitters and crocheters.
 I recently finished a hat that my cousin asked me to make for her daughter. At first I wanted to knit a hat but I decided to crochet it instead. I looked through many different patterns and had trouble finding one that I liked the most. I settled on Alpine Nights because the pattern seemed not only simple but also very pretty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Vegetarian by Han Kang</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-vegetarian-by-han-kang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 04:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-vegetarian-by-han-kang/</guid>
      <description>Yeong-hye and her husband are ordinary people. He is an office worker with moderate ambitions and mild manners; she is an uninspired but dutiful wife. The acceptable flatline of their marriage is interrupted when Yeong-hye, seeking a more &amp;#8216;plant-like&amp;rsquo; existence, decides to become a vegetarian, prompted by grotesque recurring nightmares. In South Korea, where vegetarianism is almost unheard-of and societal mores are strictly obeyed, Yeong-hye&amp;rsquo;s decision is a shocking act of subversion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m a Little Behind</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/im-a-little-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/im-a-little-behind/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days ago I was behind on my granny squares for my temperature blanket. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know, temperature blankets consist of one square a day and each square represents the temperature of that day. Thankfully, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to catch up with temperature blankets! Even though I&amp;rsquo;m caught up with the squares, I still haven&amp;rsquo;t woven the ends in yet nor have I joined them. Eek!
Last week I was babysitting my little cousin and he was playing with my yarn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tempted by Static Pages Again</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/programming/tempted-by-static-pages-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 14:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/programming/tempted-by-static-pages-again/</guid>
      <description>I recently started learning how to use emacs, which is a text editor and a Lisp interpreter. During my quest for resources, I came across a number of developers and their blogs. Since I&amp;rsquo;m always intrigued by what sort of tools developers use to make their blogs, I did a little snooping. A shocking number of people who didn&amp;rsquo;t use WordPress as their blogging platform opted for flat files instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two Steps Forward, One Step Back</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/two-steps-forward-one-step-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 03:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/two-steps-forward-one-step-back/</guid>
      <description>I finally finished one Bernat Blanket Stripes cake! I am going to move onto cake number two for my afghan ripple blanket. I don&amp;rsquo;t really know yet who this blanket will be for. My mom keeps asking me and I can&amp;rsquo;t make up my mind. I am pretty happy that I am making progress on this blanket. I might need three cakes for this though and not the two that I have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STASH Lounge Moving and Other Outings</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/stash-lounge-moving-and-other-outings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 03:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/stash-lounge-moving-and-other-outings/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday Yesterday opened up at their new location across the street. I dragged my brother along with me to the opening.
It was absolutely lovely! They had a DJ play some music in the background, a coffee bar, and a table of yummy sweets in the back. They even had door prizes, which I suspect I didn&amp;rsquo;t win anything from but that&amp;rsquo;s totally okay.
In terms of the space, it&amp;rsquo;s great!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Time Crocheting on a Road Trip</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/first-time-crocheting-on-a-road-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 15:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/first-time-crocheting-on-a-road-trip/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I went to Drumheller with the family. Up to this point I haven&amp;rsquo;t had a chance to go on a long road trip with my crochet. I started this ripple afghan a couple of days ago with Bernat Blanket Stripes yarn. This blanket is intended for my cousins&amp;rsquo;s newborn son. I guess he isn&amp;rsquo;t quite so newborn now but every baby could use a blanket regardless! I actually restarted this blanket once or twice but I finally got the hang of it while on this trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stampede Food</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/stampede-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/stampede-food/</guid>
      <description>Honestly, Stampede is synonymous with food for me. Stampede means free breakfasts for a week. Usually these breakfasts consists of pancakes and sausages. We ended up going to six of these breakfasts. Some of them were worth it, some of them weren&amp;rsquo;t. One of them actually ended up being $250 because my brother got fined for forgetting to validate his train ticket on the way to a breakfast. But still, a lot of pancakey goodness!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: God in Pink by Hasan Namir</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-god-in-pink-by-hasan-namir/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 22:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-god-in-pink-by-hasan-namir/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Topics of sexuality, religion, and spoilers for the book is mentioned in this blog post.
 A revelatory novel about being queer and Muslim, set in war-torn Iraq in 2003. Ramy is a young gay Iraqi struggling to find a balance between his sexuality, religion, and culture. Ammar is a sheikh whose guidance Ramy seeks, and whose tolerance is tested by his belief in the teachings of the Qur&amp;rsquo;an. Full of quiet moments of beauty and raw depictions of violence, God in Pink poignantly captures the anguish and the fortitude of Islamic life in Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting a Nanodegree at Udacity</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/programming/starting-a-nanodegree-at-udacity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 18:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/programming/starting-a-nanodegree-at-udacity/</guid>
      <description>While I&amp;rsquo;m still looking for a job this summer (which is almost halfway over already&amp;#8230; Blah!) I took a cue from Y who started to work on some side projects and I decided to be a little more productive. Since I have a free month of Udacity from the GitHub Student Pack. Udacity is basically an online learning hub where you can take courses that are related to the tech field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #6: My Second Granny Square</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-6-my-second-granny-square/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 04:56:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-6-my-second-granny-square/</guid>
      <description>FO means &amp;ldquo;finished object&amp;rdquo; in crochet and knitter terms. So any completed project is a finished object!
 After making my first granny square, I quickly made my second granny square. Both were made from Loop &amp;amp; Threads yarn of the wool variety. I can&amp;rsquo;t remember the exact name of the yarn.
I am not quite sure about the colour choices but they were the colours I had on hand of the same yarn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winding Yarn Multitasking</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/winding-yarn-multitasking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 10:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/winding-yarn-multitasking/</guid>
      <description>Since I recently started making a temperature blanket. I bought a couple of skeins of yarn (Bernat Premium, they are so soft!) and decided to wind them into balls to make transporting them easier for when/if I&amp;rsquo;m on the go. Surprisingly, it takes a while for them to wind up. I thought it was a perfect opportunity to watch some TV shows while doing it.
I decided to finish up watching season 2 of Knights of Sidonia, an anime about a human space colony at war with alien-like creatures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Spam Isn’t Just Annoying</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/websites/when-spam-isnt-just-annoying/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 17:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/websites/when-spam-isnt-just-annoying/</guid>
      <description>The past couple of weeks I noticed that the MySQL service on my server would routinely stop out of the blue. At first I suspected that it was because my 512MB RAM wasn&amp;rsquo;t enough but when I looked at the usage history, I never peaked more than 9%. I even tried reinstalling the MySQL server which worked at first but then it stopped running again.
However, I think the problem was due to bots trying to log into my WordPress dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Out in Pre-Stampede Rush</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/day-out-in-pre-stampede-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/day-out-in-pre-stampede-rush/</guid>
      <description>I went to the first pancake breakfast of the season with my family the other day. It was close to home which was a great bonus because my dad had the car for work. The breakfast wasn&amp;rsquo;t busy at all but maybe being fairly early was a factor. They only served pancakes and sausage patties but they were pretty good! There was also a Tim Hortons truck giving out free coffee and hot chocolate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Udacity Programming Fundamental Lesson 5: Take a Break Mini-Project</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/programming/udacity-programming-fundamental-lesson-5-take-a-break-mini-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 03:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/programming/udacity-programming-fundamental-lesson-5-take-a-break-mini-project/</guid>
      <description>Seeing that I am now unemployed and have a lot of time on my hands, I decided to utilize the free month of Udacity I received from Github&amp;rsquo;s Student Pack.
This mini-project&amp;rsquo;s goal is to create a simple program using Python to open a web browser at an interval of ten seconds three times in a row.
Here is my answer:
import time import webbrowser break_duration = 10 break_num = 3 break_count = 0 print(&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canada 150 Temperature Blanket: First Colour Change</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/canada-150-temperature-blanket-first-colour-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 22:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/canada-150-temperature-blanket-first-colour-change/</guid>
      <description>A post shared by Edel Altares (@edelgraceme) on Jul 5, 2017 at 3:41pm PDT   Since the beginning of July, I&amp;rsquo;ve been recording the highs and lows of the daily temperature through granny squares. The middle colour represents the low of the day and the outer colour represents the high of the day. The first three days of July were roughly the same but the fourth was a little bit cooler.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knitting Haul #1: LIHAO and Takumi Bamboo Needles</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/knitting/knitting-haul-1-lihao-and-takumi-bamboo-needles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/knitting/knitting-haul-1-lihao-and-takumi-bamboo-needles/</guid>
      <description>I am just starting to get into knitting as well and I decided to buy a relatively cheap set of bamboo knitting needles. I found this LIHAO Bamboo set on Amazon for around $16.99 CAD. Included are 18 pairs of needles ranging from 2.0mm to 10.0mm. It also came with a knitting gauge which is super helpful!
From a quick look over, there are no obvious defects. The reviews say that they are perfect for beginners so we&amp;rsquo;ll see!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kuzu no Honkai: On Using Others</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/anime/kuzu-no-honkai-on-using-others/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 04:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/anime/kuzu-no-honkai-on-using-others/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: There is spoilers for the entire anime and (presumably) manga. Mentions of mature themes such as sexual content is also included.
Now that classes have ended and I&amp;rsquo;m unemployed, I am taking it a little bit slow with my free time. I recently started on working a new afghan square for the month of July and watching various movies and TV shows on Amazon Prime. I stumbled across Kuzu no Honkai and while the synopsis made me skeptical, I decided to give it a shot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kits and Knits</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/kits-and-knits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 22:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/kits-and-knits/</guid>
      <description>Last week was the end of final exams and on my last exam, I decided to take a well deserved day out. In celebration of Canada Day, Tim Hortons was bringing back Roll Up the Rim for a time. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to cut down on my coffee but I decided to get at least one cup, just to try my luck. Turns out that my luck isn&amp;rsquo;t that so great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #21</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-21/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Name a book that changed your life.
 Busting out the big questions. This is a hard one to answer. I think that I&amp;rsquo;m still trying to find it. I have my favourite books but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure of their impact on my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yarn Haul #8: Gina Brown’s First Visit</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-8-gina-browns-first-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-8-gina-browns-first-visit/</guid>
      <description>I went to visit another local yarn store called Gina Brown&amp;rsquo;s. I was in the area waiting to meet up with some friends and decided to pop in and check the place out. It&amp;rsquo;s way too convenient that this place is a ten minute walk away from a train station.
It&amp;rsquo;s a nice store. In the back there&amp;rsquo;s a big table available for classes and (I&amp;rsquo;m assuming) to just knit or crochet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #20</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 07:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-20/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 If you are at a really good point in a book and the phone rings or the door bell rings, do you stop reading or let the phone or door bell go unanswered?
 Honestly, I would get up and check them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yarn Haul #7: The Knitting Room First Visit</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-7-the-knitting-room-first-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 07:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-7-the-knitting-room-first-visit/</guid>
      <description>I have been going to the Brentwood Village Mall for the past couple of years now and I have never ever noticed this nice little yarn store before until I started up crochet. The Knitting Room is a small store located in a mall close to my university. I usually go to the mall when I&amp;rsquo;m itching to walk somewhere between classes. I decided to finally visit The Knitting Room for the first time and came away with some yarn!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Vital Signs by Tessa McWatt</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-vital-signs-by-tessa-mcwatt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 10:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-vital-signs-by-tessa-mcwatt/</guid>
      <description>After thirty years of marriage, producing three now-grown children, Mike and Anna have settled into entrenched domesticity. She is skillful and poised and still beautiful, an instructor of English at the city college. He is a successful graphic artist on the verge of retirement, his awards and ambitions and accomplishments largely behind him. Though the couple’s erotic life has dimmed somewhat, he still considers her ravishing.
But their apparent balance is thrown asunder when Anna breaks the normal silence of their breakfast table with uncontrollable babble about hummingbirds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #19</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 07:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-19/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How do you organize your blog in terms of what is in your side bar? Do you have categories and defined sections in your side bar?
 At the moment, my side bar is laid out by links to my favourite bloggers, categories, monthly archives, and recent comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning How to Knit at STASH Needle Art Lounge #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/knitting/learning-how-to-knit-at-stash-needle-art-lounge-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 07:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/knitting/learning-how-to-knit-at-stash-needle-art-lounge-1/</guid>
      <description>Since I recently took up crochet, I have also been itching to start learning how to knit as well. I figure it would be advantageous to take up both of the more well known fiber art hobbies. So I signed up for lessons at one of my local yarn stores.
The store itself is very cozy and quaint. It&amp;rsquo;s literally a small house filled to the brim with yarn. The people at the front desk are extremely nice and while I was waiting for class to start, they offered me some tea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Frankenstein by Mary Shelley</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-frankenstein-by-mary-shelley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 06:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-frankenstein-by-mary-shelley/</guid>
      <description>To many readers, who have perhaps known Frankenstein only at second hand, the original may well come as a surprise. When Mary Shelley began it, she was only eighteen, though she was already Shelley&amp;rsquo;s mistress and Byron&amp;rsquo;s friend. In her preface she explains how she and Shelley spent part of a wet summer with Byron in Switzerland, amusing themselves by reading and writing ghost stories. Her contribution was Frankenstein, a story about a student of natural philosophy who learns the secret of imparting life to a creature constructed from bones he has collected in charnel-houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attempts at Cooking</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/cooking/attempts-at-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 18:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/cooking/attempts-at-cooking/</guid>
      <description>I tried to cook more during the month of May. Partly because my mother was out of the country and then cooking was left to us but also because I&amp;rsquo;m trying my best to learn how to cook. Unfortunately, most of what I cooked was pretty simple but I still managed to cook some things. I didn&amp;rsquo;t take pictures of everything I cooked, although I totally should have.
Honey Garlic Chicken Wings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #18</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 07:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-18/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 If you could have lunch with any living authors and/or book bloggers, who would you choose and why?
 Oh man, the living restriction is a tough one. If language wasn&amp;rsquo;t a barrier, I would definitely have lunch with Haruki Murakami.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hooked on Crochet Spring 2017 Swap</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/hooked-on-crochet-spring-2017-swap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 17:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/hooked-on-crochet-spring-2017-swap/</guid>
      <description>Hooked on Crochet is a Discord server that I am a part of. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what Discord is, it is essentially a chat client for gamers. You can create your own &amp;ldquo;servers&amp;rdquo; or chat rooms for dedicated topics. Hooked on Crochet is (obviously) a group of crocheters. They organized a yarn swap last spring which I took a part of.
My gifter got me a set of hand dyed Alpaca yarn, a llama stitch marker, and a pattern for a unicorn amigurumi!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Nine Island by Jane Alison</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-nine-island-by-jane-alison/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 17:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-nine-island-by-jane-alison/</guid>
      <description>Nine Island is an intimate autobiographical novel, told by J, a woman who lives in a glass tower on one of Miami Beach’s lush Venetian Islands. After decades of disaster with men, she is trying to decide whether to withdraw forever from romantic love. Having just returned to Miami from a monthlong reunion with an old flame, “Sir Gold,” and a visit to her fragile mother, J begins translating Ovid’s magical stories about the transformations caused by Eros.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #17</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 07:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-17/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do your bookshelves have books ONLY or do you also have bookish items on the shelves?
 I have books, bookish items, and non-bookish items on my shelves. Actually my shelves are in a pretty sorry state. There is a lot of clutter on them and they&amp;rsquo;re usually my go to place to put things when I have no idea where to put them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>25 Before 25: Update #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/25-before-25-update-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 01:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/25-before-25-update-1/</guid>
      <description>I took a little break during the month of May. My mental health was honestly at an all time low and I found myself having a hard time picking myself back up to get motivated to actually do things. Since I am around 6 months into my 22nd year of living, I thought it would be a good time to pause and reflect how I&amp;rsquo;m doing with my 25 before 25.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #16</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/book-blogger-hop-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/book-blogger-hop-16/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Would you stop reading a book if an element of the plot strongly clashed with your personal beliefs, or would you continue reading until you finished the book?
 I would definitely finish the book. At least, that&amp;rsquo;s what I think and hope I would do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #15</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hope-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hope-15/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 When you feature a book in your posts, do you include a book cover?
 I definitely try my best to do so. It seems a little weird to write a blog post about a book without featuring the cover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Hour at Cafe Blanca</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/an-hour-at-cafe-blanca/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 09:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/an-hour-at-cafe-blanca/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a cool hip place at the edge of Calgary&amp;rsquo;s Chinatown and across Eau Claire Market called Cafe Blanca. They&amp;rsquo;re most known for their Siphon coffee which I unfortunately did not remember to try. Instead, I ordered a plain normal latte and a cheesecake.

Now, I&amp;rsquo;m not cheesecake expert but I&amp;rsquo;m definitely a cheesecake lover. I got myself a mint chocolate cheesecake. It was extremely delicious. It was a little more cake than I prefer (the base was an actual chocolate cake and yes, cake, not brownie) and not as much cheese as I&amp;rsquo;d like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #14</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 08:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-14/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 If you could meet one author, dead or alive, who would it be? Submitted by Kristin @ Lukten av Trykksverte
 I am in love with the Brontë sisters. Their lives intrigue me a great deal and the sense of mystery surrounding them is too much for me to take at times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #5: My First Granny Square</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-5-my-first-granny-square/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2017 18:14:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-5-my-first-granny-square/</guid>
      <description>My previous FO was part of the March National Crochet Month and this one is no different. Except this event is a charity run. This square will be going to a charity to be part of a blanket! Different squares from different people will all be sewn together. I think it&amp;rsquo;s a cool joint effort!

It took me a swatch to get the hang of making a granny square. Thankfully the process is straightforward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: The Birthday of the World and Other Stories by Ursula K. Le Guin</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-birthday-of-the-world-and-other-stories-by-ursula-k-le-guin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2017 16:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-the-birthday-of-the-world-and-other-stories-by-ursula-k-le-guin/</guid>
      <description>For more than four decades, Ursula K. Le Guin has enthralled readers with her imagination, clarity, and moral vision. The recipient of numerous literary prizes, including the National Book Award, the Kafka Award, and five Hugo and five Nebula Awards, this renowned writer has, in each story and novel, created a provocative, ever-evolving universe filled with diverse worlds and rich characters reminiscent of our earthly selves.
Now, in The Birthday of the World, this gifted artist returns to these worlds in eight brilliant short works, including a never-before-published novella, each of which probes the essence of humanity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TIL: How to Set Up Virtual Hosts on Apache</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/websites/til-how-to-set-up-virtual-hosts-on-apache/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 17:50:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/websites/til-how-to-set-up-virtual-hosts-on-apache/</guid>
      <description>Create a virtual host configuration file site-name.conf for the site:
sudo vim /etc/apache2/sites-available/&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;site-name.conf&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;  Inside the file:
&amp;lt;VirtualHost *:80&amp;gt; ServerAdmin &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;email&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; ServerName &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;domain name&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; ServerAlias &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;domain name&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; DocumentRoot &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;path to folder no slash at the end&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; ErrorLog &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;path to error log&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; CustomLog &amp;lt;em&amp;gt;path to access log&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt; &amp;lt;Directory /&amp;gt; Options FollowSymLinks AllowOverride All &amp;lt;/Directory&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/VirtualHost&amp;gt;  Add the site to the host file:
sudo vim /etc/hosts  Inside the file:
127.0.0.1 localhost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #4: NatCroMo2017 Mystery Crochet Along</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-4-natcromo2017-mystery-crochet-along/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 08:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-4-natcromo2017-mystery-crochet-along/</guid>
      <description>March is National Crochet Month. A group on Ravelry holds a series of events during the month to celebrate. One of these events is a mystery crochet along! Basically, the finished product is a mystery and parts of the pattern is slowly released throughout the month.
There were times I fell a little behind the clues but I managed to finish it off! Honestly, I find it a little bit derpy but that&amp;rsquo;s part of it&amp;rsquo;s charm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #13</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 08:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-13/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you visit every listed blog in the linky list when you are participating in a meme? Submitted by Elizabeth @ Silver&amp;rsquo;s Reviews
 I try to! But I don&amp;rsquo;t always manage to do so. I usually do my blog hopping on the train to/from work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crochet Haul #6: Blanket Mania</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-6-blanket-mania/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-6-blanket-mania/</guid>
      <description>I decided to make a baby blanket for my cousin who is due in June. I bought a ton of Bernat Blanket skeins for this project. There is a big sale going on at Michael&amp;rsquo;s so I kept getting discount after discount. Which is good because I could never imagine buying this many skeins of Bernat Blanket at full price. I may have actually bought too many. I did buy one skein at Walmart though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Gamelife by Michael Clune</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-gamelife-by-michael-clune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-gamelife-by-michael-clune/</guid>
      <description>You have been awakened.
Floppy disk inserted, computer turned on, a whirring, and then this sentence, followed by a blinking cursor. So begins Suspended, the first computer game to obsess seven-year-old Michael, to worm into his head and change his sense of reality. Thirty years later he will write: &amp;ldquo;Computer games have taught me the things you can&amp;rsquo;t learn from people.&amp;rdquo;
Gamelife is the memoir of a childhood transformed by technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #3: Dot’s Little Ditty Bag – Perpetually Loading</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-3-dots-little-ditty-bag-perpetually-loading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 19:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-3-dots-little-ditty-bag-perpetually-loading/</guid>
      <description>I made this little bag mostly while playing the MMO Blade &amp;amp; Soul, hence the title &amp;ldquo;Perpetually Loading.&amp;rdquo; My computer is a bit of a toaster so I managed to get a lot of crocheting done while on the loading screen. Sometimes my game would crash on the loading screen and that would mean even more crocheting for me! Unfortunately, this worked out to the disadvantage of my SO who I was playing with at the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paint Nite Calgary at Yuk Yuk’s Comedy Club</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/paint-nite-at-yuk-yuks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 07:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/paint-nite-at-yuk-yuks/</guid>
      <description>One of the interns at my workplace suggested going painting as an activity that we could all do together. It seemed fun so we decided to give it a try! Paint Nite is a series of painting events held at bars, each session hosted by different people.
That day we went to Yuk Yuk&amp;rsquo;s Comedy Club which is a few minutes walk from Victoria Park Stampede. We were really confused about the food since there was no (or incorrect) information on the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #12</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 06:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-12/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How do you handle negative comments left on your blog? Submitted by Maria @ A Night&amp;rsquo;s Dream of Books
 Thankfully, I haven&amp;rsquo;t encountered this problem before. 🙂 And if I have, obviously I must have handled it well because it didn&amp;rsquo;t make a lasting impression on me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crochet Haul #5: First Michael’s Trip</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-5-first-michaels-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 12:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-5-first-michaels-trip/</guid>
      <description>I recently found out that there was a Michael&amp;rsquo;s near my workplace. Rookie mistake. After work, I walked over to the store. It&amp;rsquo;s a 20 minute walk in an area with absolutely no sidewalks. The snow hindered me a little bit but not enough to make me turn away!
Okay, this is actually my second Michael&amp;rsquo;s yarn trip but the first time, I didn&amp;rsquo;t buy a single thing. I just went to check out the place and see the different kinds of brands they had.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tip: Backing Up MySQL Databases Via Command Line</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/programming/tip-backing-up-mysql-databases-via-command-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 19:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/programming/tip-backing-up-mysql-databases-via-command-line/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt; &amp;lt;pre&amp;gt;mysqldump -u username -p database &amp;gt; backup_name.sql&amp;lt;/pre&amp;gt; &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;
I always forget this command. I always try to attempt to go mysql dump instead of mysqldump. Hopefully posting this little blurb will give me an easy reference in the future!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Reivew: Manga Classics – Emma by Stacy King</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-reivew-manga-classics-emma-by-stacy-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 21:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-reivew-manga-classics-emma-by-stacy-king/</guid>
      <description>Just in time for the 200th Anniversary, Manga Classics: Emma brings Jane Austen&amp;rsquo;s classic tale of youthful folly and romantic exuberance to a modern audience with this beautiful, new manga adaptation. The impulsive match-making of Emma Woodhouse delivers both humor and heartache through the gorgeous artwork of manga-ka Po Tse (Manga Classics: Pride and Prejudice). &amp;#8211; Manga Classics editions feature classic stories, faithfully adapted and illustrated in manga style, and available in both hardcover and softcover editions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #2: Easy and Thin Dishcloth</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-2-easy-and-thin-dishcloth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 12:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-2-easy-and-thin-dishcloth/</guid>
      <description>This next dishcloth I made was a simple green dishcloth with single crochets. What initially drew me to the pattern was that the texture of the dishcloth was very pretty. I was surprised to know that the variance in texture was simple due to changing which loop you inserted the hook in! While it isn&amp;rsquo;t completely perfect, by the time I finished this I felt a lot more confident in my single crochets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #11</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2017 06:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-11/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Do you read a lot of diverse or own voices books? Why or why not? Submitted by Kitty @ Vicarious Bookworm
 Hmm&amp;#8230; I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what this question means so I&amp;rsquo;m going to take a stab at it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crochet Haul #4: HiKoo Simplicity</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-4-hikoo-simplicity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-4-hikoo-simplicity/</guid>
      <description>I made a post about participating in Crochet Along Together (CAT) to make a three colour cowl and the yarn I ordered for the project finally arrived! It was good timing too because the event started the next day. I was getting a little worried that it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t arrive in time.
Despite the discount I got on the yarn due specifically to the CAT (the CAT was sponsored by this brand, I think), it was kind of pricey for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review: Amity by Nasreen Pevjak</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-amity-by-nasreen-pevjak/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2017 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-review-amity-by-nasreen-pevjak/</guid>
      <description>Amity provides a window to the wreckage caused by wars—the destruction and displacement that leave pain and life-long psychological disorders, here specifically within the contexts of Yugoslavia’s dissolution and Iran’s revolution.
Payvand, an Iranian refugee and activist, still plagued with nightmares, meets a Ragusa, a Yugoslavian refugee whose pockets are loaded with stones as she prepares to walk into the water and end her life, a life that has become intolerable since the loss of those most dear to her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art, Food, and Good Old Bowling</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/art-food-and-good-old-bowling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 09:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/art-food-and-good-old-bowling/</guid>
      <description>At the company where I&amp;rsquo;m doing an internship right now offered all the interns the opportunity to go to their downtown location and give us a tour of all the art. It seems a little weird to give art tours in an office environment but once we stepped into the building, it made sense. There was art on every single floor of the building (of which there are over ten floors) and almost every single wall has a piece of art hanging on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #10</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 08:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-10/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How far in advance do you read the books you have scheduled for review?
 I don&amp;rsquo;t read books &amp;ldquo;ahead of time.&amp;rdquo; I just read books with no schedule in mind and review them as I go. I guess this question is geared towards the more veteran book bloggers who recieve copies of books to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crochet Haul #3: Vanna’s Choice in Silver Grey Yarn</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-3-vannas-choice-in-silver-grey-yarn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2017 21:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-3-vannas-choice-in-silver-grey-yarn/</guid>
      <description>When I bought my crochet hook set, I needed to buy an additional $15 worth of products so I could get free shipping. It saved me around five dollars and there was no point in getting hooks without any yarn.
Unfortunately, they shipped it separate from the hooks but I had bought yarn from Walmart in the meantime while waiting for my things to arrive.
So here is the skein of yarn I got from Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Crochet Month 2017: Mystery Crochet Along Clues 1 &amp; 2</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/national-crochet-month-2017-mystery-crochet-along-clues-1-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 20:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/national-crochet-month-2017-mystery-crochet-along-clues-1-2/</guid>
      <description>The group []() on Ravelry are holding an MCAL (Mystery Crochet Along) which I am taking part of. The project is an amigurumi. I have never made an amigurumi before and this will be my first! It will be interesting seeing that I have no idea what the finished project will look like. These are the first two clues finished. I still need to start clue 3 and 4, I&amp;rsquo;m a little behind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FO #1: Corchet Guru Dishcloth</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-1-corchet-guru-dishcloth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2017 21:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/fo-1-corchet-guru-dishcloth/</guid>
      <description>On February 26 I finished my very first project! It&amp;rsquo;s only a simple dishcloth as I&amp;rsquo;m just starting out. I know the colours are kind of garish but I never thought I&amp;rsquo;d be using them together until I actually started working on it. I can see some of the mistakes I made, and there are many, but I am extremely happy with how it turned out and I had a lot of fun making it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #9</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 08:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-9/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 When you start reading a novel, do you prefer to be plunged right into the action, or do you prefer a slower, more descriptive introduction to the plot and characters? Submitted by Maria @ [
 
Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Can I Get Coffee After Five in this City?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/where-can-i-get-coffee-after-five-in-this-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 05:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/where-can-i-get-coffee-after-five-in-this-city/</guid>
      <description>I found myself in downtown with cancelled plans the other day. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to be home for another two hours so I decided to try a new coffee place. It was around five in the evening. I pulled up Google Maps and searched for coffee.
Scrolling through the list, I found that most of the coffee places closed at 5:00PM or 6:00PM. I needed a place to sit and blog hop for a little bit so that was no good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planned Projects for March 2017</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/planned-projects-for-march-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 12:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/planned-projects-for-march-2017/</guid>
      <description>As you may have noticed, I recently took up learning how to crochet. Since March is National Crochet Month, &amp;nbsp;I decided to take part in some of the activities that are being held at Ravelry.
MCAL (Mystery Crochet Along)
This is an event that reveals the pattern slowly, clue by clue. The only hint is that it&amp;rsquo;s an anigurumi made out of three colours. This will be my first amigurumi so I&amp;rsquo;m quite excited but also anxious that it won&amp;rsquo;t turn out well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crochet Haul #2: Cheap Crochet Set</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-2-cheap-crochet-set/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 13:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-haul-2-cheap-crochet-set/</guid>
      <description>Since I&amp;rsquo;m just starting out with crocheting, I bought a somewhat cheap crochet set on Amazon. I&amp;rsquo;m hesitant to buy high end luxury tools if I&amp;rsquo;m not even sure I want to continue crocheting. I do think it would be a worthy hobby to take part in!
The case itself is seriously cute. The brand seems to be Merrywindix but I can&amp;rsquo;t quite tell. It&amp;rsquo;s a lot smaller than I expected which is great, that means it&amp;rsquo;s extremely portable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crochet Along Together #1: Easy as 1-2-3 Cowl (Part 1)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-along-together-1-easy-as-1-2-3-cowl-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/crochet-along-together-1-easy-as-1-2-3-cowl-part-1/</guid>
      <description>The fine folks at Skacel Knitting are hosting a series they call &amp;ldquo;Crochet Along Together&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;CAT&amp;rdquo; for short. They post videos throughout the month to walk you through the project. A draw is also held after the project is finished.
March CAT
This is their very first installment and is geared towards (but not limited to) beginners to crochet. The project for this months is the Easy As 1-2-3 Cowl which is a three colour cowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #8</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 08:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-8/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How do you feel about books with multiple narrators? Submitted by Eli @ The Book Supplier
 I definitely don&amp;rsquo;t mind them nor do I have a preference towards them. My opinion isn&amp;rsquo;t fresh as I haven&amp;rsquo;t read a book with multiple narrators in a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ending of Arrival</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/movies/the-ending-of-arrival/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2017 20:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/movies/the-ending-of-arrival/</guid>
      <description>I finally got to watch Arrival the other day. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t exactly everything that I expected but I think I wasn&amp;rsquo;t displeased with the twist.
The fist half of the movie follows Louise, a professor who specializes in languages and translations. She is recruited by the government to help translate the language of aliens who had touched down on earth. Together with a mathematician, Ian, they slowly learn the writing system of the aliens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning the Guitar: Week 1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/music/learning-the-guitar-week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 01:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/music/learning-the-guitar-week-1/</guid>
      <description>I have been following Justin Guitar&amp;#8216;s lesson plans for learning the guitar.
This week I went through the first 15 beginner&amp;rsquo;s course lessons, BC-101 to BC-115. I learned the basics of choosing a guitar, posture, etc. In terms of actually playing, I learned the D chord, A chord, and E chord. The first two chords were incredibly &amp;ldquo;easy.&amp;rdquo; The chord that really stumped me was the E chord. I could not press down on the strings hard enough so that it didn&amp;rsquo;t sound muted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Cheesecake Quest</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/cooking/homemade-cheesecake-quest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 16:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/cooking/homemade-cheesecake-quest/</guid>
      <description>I can count the number of times I have tried to make cheesecake on one hand. It&amp;rsquo;s not that many but I count that as a quest to make the ultimate cheesecake. It&amp;rsquo;s my favourite dessert. Yes, it&amp;rsquo;s incredibly filling and calorie dense and expensive but I love it. The expensiveness factor is a big reason why I&amp;rsquo;m trying to perfect the art of the cheesecake.
On my first attempt back in high school, it tasted lke cream cheese on a graham cracker crust.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #7 (02/17-02/23)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-7-0217-0223/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2017 13:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-7-0217-0223/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Can you read and watch TV or listen to the radio at the same time? Submitted by Elizabeth @ [Silver&amp;rsquo;s Reviews]()
 Nope! Unless we&amp;rsquo;re talking about dry, academic textbooks. I can read the words but nothing will go into my head.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it Possible to Read Too Much?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/is-it-possible-to-read-too-much/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 02:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/is-it-possible-to-read-too-much/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m in a weird place where I&amp;rsquo;m reading a lot but I&amp;rsquo;m unsure if I&amp;rsquo;m feeling depressed because I&amp;rsquo;m reading too much or I&amp;rsquo;m reading too much because I&amp;rsquo;m feeling depressed.
I&amp;rsquo;ve always thought of books as an escape. That sounds a little too negative but I enjoy experiencing a story that I would probably never experience myself. Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve gravitated to historical fiction because it&amp;rsquo;s just so different and unknown territory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #6 (02/10-02/16)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-6-0210-0216/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 20:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-6-0210-0216/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 What is your favorite Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day read? Submitted by Kristin @ Lukten av Trykksverte
 Is it okay for me to say that I don&amp;rsquo;t have any&amp;#8230;? I don&amp;rsquo;t really read anything specifically for Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day. I also don&amp;rsquo;t recall any Valentine&amp;rsquo;s Day themed books.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Joined a Gym</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/i-joined-a-gym/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/i-joined-a-gym/</guid>
      <description>In an attempt to do more things in my free time, I decided to join a gym. My original plan was to go to my university gym however since I am on co-op, I no longer have the discounted membership included in my tuition. Instead, I opted for my local Fit4Less. It is an extremely more convenient location, significantly cheaper, and a good &amp;ldquo;introductory&amp;rdquo; gym for those who are just starting out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #5 (02/03-02/09)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-5-0203-0209/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 20:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-5-0203-0209/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Read or Clean? Read or Bake? Read or Make Dinner? What would be your choice? Submitted by Elizabeth @ Silver&amp;rsquo;s Reviews
 There are quite a lot of questions for today!
 Read or Clean? If I play my cards right, both!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Drawing #3</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/weekly-drawing-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 02:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/weekly-drawing-3/</guid>
      <description>Last week&amp;rsquo;s theme was fantasy. The original picture was a lot more ethereal and pretty. I had to redraw this one because I messed up the background. The background was definitely the hardest part because the original picture relied heavily on colour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Minimalist Bullet Journal for 2017</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/organization/my-minimalist-bullet-journal-for-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 18:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/organization/my-minimalist-bullet-journal-for-2017/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a couple of weeks since 2017 has started. I started off the new year with some tweaks to my bullet journal. 2016 wasn&amp;rsquo;t the best year for using my bullet journal. I used it a lot when I was in school but not so much when I was working. I&amp;rsquo;m aiming to be more productive outside of work this year though! In light of my new goal, I decided it was best to revamp my bullet journal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #4 (01/27-02/02/2017)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-4-0127-02022017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-4-0127-02022017/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 How many books have you statted but just couldn&amp;rsquo;t finish? Submitted by Elizabeth @ Silver&amp;rsquo;s Reviews
 How many? As in, a specific number? Too many to count. Actually, that&amp;rsquo;s not accurate. I don&amp;rsquo;t really know the answer to that question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Listened To: Electra Heart by Marina and the Diamonds</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/music/i-listened-to-electra-heart-by-marina-and-the-diamonds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/music/i-listened-to-electra-heart-by-marina-and-the-diamonds/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: Lyrics relating to suicide is mentioned in this post.
Another disclaimer: I&amp;rsquo;m not good at writing reviews but I do like expressing my opinions. This is in no way a professional review but rather how I personally feel about this album.
I know Marina and the Diamonds&amp;rsquo; album Electra Heart is one of her personally least favourite works but I like it a lot. Many people think Electra Heart represents an alter-ego but it&amp;rsquo;s rather a personality that Marina holds in disdain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #3 (01/20-01/26/2017)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-3-0120-01262017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-3-0120-01262017/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 What was the one time you thought the movie was better than the book? Submitted by Tomi @ A Bookworm&amp;rsquo;s Guide to Life
 Okay, this is a really tough one. I am sure I have watched plenty of book movies but I haven&amp;rsquo;t always read the book counterpart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Watched: Rogue One</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/movies/i-saw-rogue-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2017 03:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/movies/i-saw-rogue-one/</guid>
      <description>Spoilers, beware.
I am not a huge Star Wars fan. I watched the first trilogy very quickly, bits and pieces of the second trilogy, and The Force Awakens. Honestly, most of what I know about Star Wars is from the Lego video games and Family Guy. However, my lack of knowledge of the franchise didn&amp;rsquo;t stop me from going to the theaters and watching the latest installment.
When I first watched the Rogue One trailer, I was left wanting for a little more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Read: Mary and The Wrongs of Woman by Mary Wollstonecraft</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/i-read-mary-and-the-wrongs-of-woman-by-mary-wollstonecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 03:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/i-read-mary-and-the-wrongs-of-woman-by-mary-wollstonecraft/</guid>
      <description>I recently finished reading Mary and The Wrongs of Woman by Mary Wollstonecraft. I received this book from a friend of my mothers. I actually received multiple books from my mother&amp;rsquo;s friend, many of them classics such as Villette by Charlotte Bronte, Emma by Jane Austen, Frankenstein by Mary Shelly (who is, by the way, the daughter of Mary Wollstonecraft), etc. I managed to find many books that I enjoyed from her gift.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Icing Charades</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/cookie-icing-charades/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 06:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/cookie-icing-charades/</guid>
      <description>The Game
Take turns to ice an object or living being onto a cookie. Everyone guesses what that person iced onto the cookie. There are no winners, just a bunch of people having fun and joking around about their lack of (or possession of) artistic ability.
The Background
Over the holidays I was baking brownies and cookies with my cousins. The brownies had left over frosting so we decided to ice the cookies with cool designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favourite Book of 2016</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/my-favourite-book-of-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 02:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/my-favourite-book-of-2016/</guid>
      <description>This is very long overdue but I was blog hopping and came across The Daily Prophecy ran by Mel. Her latest post was a quick survey of all the books she read in 2016. At the end of her post, she posed the question:
 What is the best book you read in 2016?
 This is a very tough question for me to answer. I read a couple of very good books this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #2 (01/13-01/19/2017)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-2-0113-01192017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop-2-0113-01192017/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Is everyday a reading day for you? Submitted by Elizabeth @ Silver&amp;rsquo;s Reviews
 I&amp;rsquo;m trying to make it a habit of reading everyday. Realistically though, I only really read during the work week. Those days I specifically block out times for myself dedicated for reading: on the way to and from work (since I take public transportation).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phew… I Moved My Fanlistings</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/websites/phew-i-moved-my-fanlistings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 14:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/websites/phew-i-moved-my-fanlistings/</guid>
      <description>Fanlistings are basically the early 2000&amp;rsquo;s version of Facebook pages. I own a bunch of them, mostly of songs or video game characters. Honestly, the whole fanlisting thing has been going down in popularity as the years go by. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit sad. Fanlistings come and go a lot. There&amp;rsquo;s a high turnover rate. I try my best to maintain and keep mine up and running.
However, my old domain name expired and I had trouble getting in touch with my registrar to renew it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #1 (01/06-01/12/2017)</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 08:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/books/book-blogger-hop/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Where&amp;rsquo;s your favourite place to read? Submitted by Ronyell @ Rabbit Ears Book Blog
 I will be honest&amp;#8230; I don&amp;rsquo;t think I have a favourite place, as long as I&amp;rsquo;m reading. In terms of places where I usually read is on the bus or when I&amp;rsquo;m eating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TIL: IGMP</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/networking/til-igmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 02:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/networking/til-igmp/</guid>
      <description>Today I learned about IGMP, which stands for Internet Group Message Protocol. There are three different ways packets are sent out to other devices. There&amp;rsquo;s unicast, which just sends a packet to one specific device. Then there&amp;rsquo;s broadcast, which sends packets to all the devices that is in the network. Lastly, there&amp;rsquo;s multicast. Multicast sends packets to more than one device but not all the devices.
If a device wants to be part of a multicast group, it sends out an IGMP packet, or more specifically, an IGMP join packet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TIL: Adding Policies in Cisco Firewalls</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/networking/til-adding-policies-in-cisco-firewalls/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 05:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/networking/til-adding-policies-in-cisco-firewalls/</guid>
      <description>Identify traffic with an access-list
access-list acl-name permit ip source destination dscp dscp-value Apply the access-list with the dscp value to an interfact
class-map match-all interface match ip dscp dscp-value Apply the policy
policy-map map-name class class-name [bandwidth bandwidth-value] [priority priority-level] set ip dscp dscp-value Today at work I was going over firewalls. We want to check the configuration of the firewalls and compare them to our QoS standards. I&amp;rsquo;m not too familiar with how policies and QoS are implemented on Cisco devices so it was pretty interesting to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to Work…</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/back-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 03:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/back-to-work/</guid>
      <description>The holidays are officially over, for I went back to work today. It was a bit of a slow day. I got my internship extended, however they basically treated me as a new hire since my contract ended in December. So I&amp;rsquo;m starting from scratch, essentially. I had no laptop, no e-mail, no account to login into any computer connected to the company&amp;rsquo;s network&amp;#8230; Kinda rough.
However, I did manage to do some small tasks that didn&amp;rsquo;t require the use of a computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TIL: How to Add a MySQL User</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/programming/til-how-to-add-a-mysql-user/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 04:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/programming/til-how-to-add-a-mysql-user/</guid>
      <description>CREATE USER &#39;user&#39;@&#39;server&#39; IDENTIFIED BY &#39;PASSWORD&#39;; GRANT PRIVILEGES ON database.table TO &#39;user&#39;@&#39;server&#39;; I recently bought a VPS from Ramnode and started tinkering on it. I needed to create a database for my fanlistings. Back when I was on shared hosting, I would use cPanel and phpMyAdmin to do all that. This is admittedly another TIL that I didn&amp;rsquo;t learn today but, rather, relearned today because the information slipped my mind. Maybe I need to rename this little segment to &amp;ldquo;TIRL.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>25 Before 25</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/25-before-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 19:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/25-before-25/</guid>
      <description>New Years Resolutions are no longer the in thing. I recently turned 22 and it feels like my life is whizzing by now. I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about my goals but there are just too many that I have for one year and a couple that will go beyond 2017. So I figured a 25 before 25 would be appropriate.
1. Graduate from university
I&amp;rsquo;ve been in university since I was 17.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2017 Reading Resolutions</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/2017-reading-resolutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 05:22:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/2017-reading-resolutions/</guid>
      <description>This year I told myself I would read at least 25 books. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem like a lot but when you consider my reading history the past couple of years, that&amp;rsquo;s a big number.
 2015: 7 books + 3 graphic novels = 10 books 2014: 19 books + 20 graphic novels = 39 books 2013: 40 books + 30 graphic novels = 74 books 2012: 18 books  As you can see, not great numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At the Library #13</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/at-the-library-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 04:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/at-the-library-13/</guid>
      <description>I recently made a trip to the library. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I managed to grab.
Buried in Books: A Reader&amp;rsquo;s Anthology by Julie Rugg
There are quite a lot of books on my to-read list that I don&amp;rsquo;t recall exactly why they&amp;rsquo;re on the list. But I trust myself if a book is on the list. I actually culled off the more obvious ones but the ones that stayed are ones that really interest me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Just Culled My Book Wish List</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/i-just-culled-my-book-wish-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 02:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/i-just-culled-my-book-wish-list/</guid>
      <description>On Goodreads, my &amp;ldquo;want-to-own&amp;rdquo; shelf used to have 127 books in it. Now it has five.
Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve been bit by the konmari bug. I&amp;rsquo;ve konmari&amp;rsquo;d my wardrobe and my books so far. I&amp;rsquo;m still stuck on the books. I decided it would be fitting to prevent my book collection from growing back to it&amp;rsquo;s ridiculous size and get rid of anything that doesn&amp;rsquo;t spark joy on my book wish list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At the Library #12</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/at-the-library-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 04:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/at-the-library-12/</guid>
      <description>I recently resolved not to take out any library books unless they were on my to read list. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I took out on my latest trip to the library!
Speak by Laurie Halse Anderson
I don&amp;rsquo;t remember why or how this book got onto my to read list but I know that it&amp;rsquo;s been on the list for quite a while. I was glad to see the book sitting on the shelf since I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading: The Secret Diaries of Charlotte Brontë</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/reading-the-secret-diaries-of-charlotte-bronte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 13:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/reading-the-secret-diaries-of-charlotte-bronte/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m extremely fond of Charlotte Brontë. Villette is easily my favourite novel and I hold it very close to my heart. A couple week ago I finally got around to reading Jane Eyre and it did not disappoint. The other members of the Brontë family are not to be overlooked either. I enjoyed Emily&amp;rsquo;s Wuthering Heights and all of Anne&amp;rsquo;s books are in my to read list. So when I stumbled upon The Secret Diaries of Charlotte Brontë by Syrie James in the library, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t resist picking it up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Week, New Me</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/new-week-new-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 04:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/new-week-new-me/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I had eaten two plates piled high with sweet American-Chinese prepared meats, a plate full of sweet desserts, and a take-out box of homemade cookies. On Friday I almost consumed an entire bag of buttery popcorn but the bag spilled into the aisle as it descended up the movie theatre steps. As I heard the small popped kernels tumble out of the bag, I felt both relief and disappointment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100 Books Every Man Should Read</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/100-books-every-man-should-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 01:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/100-books-every-man-should-read/</guid>
      <description>The Art of Manliness put out this list of books. I am not a man but we&amp;rsquo;ll see how I do with this list. Turns I&amp;rsquo;ve only read 8% of this list. Out of the books I want to read from this list, I&amp;rsquo;ve read 24%. Not any better, but hey. I&amp;rsquo;m really trying to cull the books I want to read though. I will never be able to read everything I want to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Silly Mistakes</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/silly-mistakes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 22:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/silly-mistakes/</guid>
      <description>At work I&amp;rsquo;m writing a simple script in Python that pulls data from a sqlite database. I was doing some inserts and deletes and I was wondering why the database wasn&amp;rsquo;t changing. I tried printing out the queries and double checking that they were indeed correct syntax-wise. I traced my program line by line up to the point where queries were being executed. Finally, I turned to Google.
Stackoverflow, of course, delivered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overheard at Work #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/overheard-at-work-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 01:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/overheard-at-work-1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Thank you Doritos, bringing families together.&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LFTP Fatal Error: Certificate verification</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/lftp-fatal-error-certificate-verification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 01:48:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/lftp-fatal-error-certificate-verification/</guid>
      <description>The error: ~$ git-ftp pull&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; ~$ cd: Fatal error: Certificate verification: certificate common name doesn&amp;rsquo;t match requested host name ‘ftp.mazohyst.org’&amp;lt;br /&amp;gt; ~$ mirror: Fatal error: Certificate verification: certificate common name doesn&amp;rsquo;t match requested host name ‘ftp.mazohyst.org’
Solution: Edit ~/.lftp/rc so that it contains set ssl:check-hostname no. What this does is pretty self explanatory. If the hostname in the certificate does not match the hostname you&amp;rsquo;re attempting to connect to, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter because it won&amp;rsquo;t check for that in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bought Some New Music!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/bought-some-new-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2016 03:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/bought-some-new-music/</guid>
      <description>Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Spotify a lot. I only ever use it when I&amp;rsquo;m at my computer. When I&amp;rsquo;m on the go, I turn to my trusty iPod classic. Since I use the free version of Spotify (now that I have a job, I can&amp;rsquo;t say that I&amp;rsquo;m a broke college student anymore but I can say that I&amp;rsquo;m still cheap), being able to choose what I listen to is a must and Spotify mobile doesn&amp;rsquo;t have that ability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speaking of Security</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/speaking-of-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 22:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/speaking-of-security/</guid>
      <description>My last post was about security by obscurity and I talked a little about trying to implement security techniques into my projects. This is really great timing.
Last week, various online services ran by my university were down. It was really inconvenient not having access to my e-mail but I took it in stride. I figured it was just the servers acting up or malware or something like that. It turns out that my university was dealing with a ransomware attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security By Obscurity: Just Hide It?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/security-by-obscurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2016 03:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/security-by-obscurity/</guid>
      <description>Last semester I took an introductory course to information security. One of the concepts we touched on was &amp;ldquo;security by obscurity.&amp;rdquo; Basically what that means is if no one is aware of something, they can&amp;rsquo;t possibly break into it. For example, hiding your diary is a form of security by obscurity. Of course, this has it flaws. There is always the possibility that someone could somehow stumble upon your diary by accident.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CCNA1 8.2.1.4 Packet Tracer – Designing and Implementing a VLSM Addressing Scheme</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/ccna1-8-2-1-4-packet-tracer-designing-and-implementing-a-vlsm-addressing-scheme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2016 06:07:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/ccna1-8-2-1-4-packet-tracer-designing-and-implementing-a-vlsm-addressing-scheme/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently taking the CCNA1 course offered by Cisco. I struggled a lot with this activity so I thought it would be good to share how I finally figured it out. If you&amp;rsquo;re a little lazy and just want the answers, click here to go straight to the addressing table or here to download the PDF. Be aware that the addresses may vary but the process is the same regardless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 28</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 19:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-28/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 28: Rest Day Oh my goodness, today is the last day of the fitness calendar! I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I made it! I didn&amp;rsquo;t make this cookie (I haven&amp;rsquo;t made any of the rest day recipes) but like with the rest of the recipes, I would love to try this eventually!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 27</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 04:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-27/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 27: Total Body Today is the last day of the beginner&amp;rsquo;s workout calendar, not including the rest day tomorrow! I think I&amp;rsquo;ll make a blog post the day after rest day to talk about how the month went. As for today, today was a lot of sweat and groaning! A lot of cardio today, even if it isn&amp;rsquo;t intensive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 26</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 05:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-26/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 26: Abs Video 1: Train Insane HIIT Workout  Video 2: Muffintop Shredder Workout I can&amp;rsquo;t remember anymore but I think I&amp;rsquo;ve done this video before. This video is really simple, there is just one move: the candlestick. I think I was doing it properly this time because I started to get tired and I could feel burning in my limbs and my core (I can&amp;rsquo;t be as technical as Cassey, what are my obliques?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 25</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 06:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-25/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 25: Lower Body Video 1: Far Burning Cardio Warmup I&amp;rsquo;ve done this video so many times that I&amp;rsquo;ve almost memorized everything Cassey said, haha! The moves in this video are easy and fun, as always.
 Video 2: Hips Butt &amp;#8216;n Thighs Super Shaper Workout   Hot Potato: This is a nice and easy move to start off the video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 24</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 05:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-24/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 24: Lower Body I&amp;rsquo;m still behind&amp;#8230; Oh well, I mostly caught up today. I still have one video to do for day 25 but it&amp;rsquo;s day 25 now and I have three hours left to do it! Today was pretty hard but that could be due to the fact I did two days in one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 23</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 07:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-23/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 23: Abs Okay I&amp;rsquo;m pretty behind. It&amp;rsquo;s now past midnight, I should be doing day 25 today. I&amp;rsquo;m waking up early tomorrow so I&amp;rsquo;ll have to skip out on catching up on day 24 until later in the day. Yesterday (two days ago?) I came home late with a huge head ache and immediately fell asleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 22</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2016 07:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-22/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 22: Total Body I was so close to not doing today&amp;rsquo;s workout because I came home late from a volunteering gig with a raging head ache. I slept for about four hours and woke up around 10:30. It took me a while to get started with the workout, I didn&amp;rsquo;t start until 11:15 and I finished at 11:55!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 21</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 06:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-21/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 21: Rest Day Today was a much needed rest day. Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been having the tendency to fall asleep as soon as I get home, which sucks. So I decided to just sleep, haha! I didn&amp;rsquo;t try out the pizza. Maybe one day. Seriously, one day I will try all of her recipes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 20</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 05:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-20/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 19: Total Body I got home today after writing a midterm and I was so tired that I was tempted to just not do the workout today but then I realized tomorrow os rest day and who wants to work out on rest day? Not me. So I decided against it and got off my butt to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 19</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 02:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-19/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 19: Abs I loathe ab days. They&amp;rsquo;re really hard and not that fun, haha. But I really do feel the burn the most on these days. I need to work on this&amp;#8230;
Video 1: Fun Indoor Cardio Workout There are A LOT of kicks in this video. I did my workout in the morning today so I had to do some modifications, as always.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 18</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 06:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-18/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 18: Lower Body Because I had to make up day 17 today, I broke the two workouts up throughout the day. But near the end of the day, I just did the last two videos all at once. This day&amp;rsquo;s workout is surprisingly not that bad. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have any trouble with the moves today which was&amp;#8230; Weird but satisfying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 17</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 04:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-17/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 17: Total Body Okay, this is the first time I have skipped a day and had to make it up. I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel too guilty about skipping yesterday because I had spin class, which is two (maybe even three) times as long and 234204398 times harder than these workouts. I enjoy spin class though, don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 16</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 06:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-16/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 16: Abs Okay, this is the first day that I technically did not do on the right day. I started this one a little after midnight because I was working on an assignment and then I looked at the time&amp;#8230; Whoops, the day went by fast! Today&amp;rsquo;s videos were okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 15</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 06:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-15/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 15: Total Body My body issues seem to have improved, minus the random headaches. I tried my best to stay active and not give into my pain. I might have to go to the doctor tomorrow though, if it gets any worse. Both videos today contained moves that were not named so I&amp;rsquo;m not going to bother with going through each move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 14</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 04:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-14/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 14: Rest Day Ummm, what?? It&amp;rsquo;s rest day already?? I do not believe it. I&amp;rsquo;ve been at this for two weeks now! I feel proud of myself, I never thought I would be able to make it this far. I&amp;rsquo;m officially halfway through the calendar! I decided not to do a workout video today because I&amp;rsquo;ve been so tired and lethargic lately and all of my limbs feel sore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 13</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 06:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-13/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 13: Total Body Video 1: 5 Minute Fat Burner &amp;ldquo;Five minutes? Easy peasey.&amp;rdquo; I was so wrong! Cassey wasn&amp;rsquo;t lying when she said it would be tough. This was a hard video, with lots of suffering included (guaranteed).
  Star Jump: These were really hard to do quietly. I definitely started sweating immediately with this move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 12</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-12/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 12: Abs Ab workouts are so brutal&amp;#8230; And, of course, that&amp;rsquo;s what everyone wants to workout. Cue the suffering.
Video 1: Ab &amp;amp; Butt Workout I seriously cannot get over how cute Rosanna is! She is absolutely adorable and when she struggles, I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m not alone in ab hell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 11</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 14:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-11/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 11: Lower Body Another day, another week almost finished (I&amp;rsquo;m talking in terms of the weekday week and not the Blogilates week)! I keep mixing up the &amp;ldquo;Wake up and &amp;#8230;&amp;rdquo; preambles at the start of each day&amp;#8230;. Yesterday I did 30 second planks on each side instead of just 1 minute of planking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 10</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calenday-2-0-day-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 06:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calenday-2-0-day-10/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 10: Abs The day starts off with two thirty second planks on each side. How I hate planks&amp;#8230; But I did it anyway, even if I cheated for a couple seconds on each. There&amp;rsquo;s only one new video today and I decided that I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t list all the moves for the other videos again in the interest of time and because I don&amp;rsquo;t really have anything to say about specific moves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 9</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 06:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-9/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 9: Abs Video 1: Total Body Workout I&amp;rsquo;m not going to list the moves for this video again because my comments are mostly the same from the last time I did this video. I really am progressing with those pull ups. Not once did I have to grab my legs!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 8</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 06:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-8/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 8: Total Body After my &amp;ldquo;rest day&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;ve been missing Cassey a little. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe that it&amp;rsquo;s already the second week! It doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel like it&amp;rsquo;s been that long&amp;#8230;
Video 1: Indoor Cardio Workout I wish I had more time to do workouts in the morning because when it comes to the cardio videos, I just can&amp;rsquo;t do them 100% without making a bunch of noise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 7</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 06:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-7/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 7: Rest Day Thank goodness for the rest day. Technically there is 30 minutes left of day 7 and I feel like I should be doing something. So I&amp;rsquo;m searching for some quick videos to do before midnight hits. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I&amp;rsquo;ve done a week of this already! Here&amp;rsquo;s to four more weeks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 6</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 01:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-6/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 6: Total Body &amp;ldquo;Wake up and do 15 crunches.&amp;rdquo; I did four roll ups instead. And I never do these when I wake up, usually it&amp;rsquo;s the last thing I do before bed. Not today though!
Video 1: Cardio Warmup I&amp;rsquo;m really glad Cassey puts some cardio videos because most of her workouts are focusing on toning and my main goal is to burn fat and not really &amp;ldquo;bulk&amp;rdquo; up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 5</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 07:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-5/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 5: Abs Okay I switched up the preambles in the calendar because apparently I can&amp;rsquo;t read. Day three I was supposed to plank for 30 seconds, yesterday I was supposed to do the burpees, and today I was supposed to drink an 8 oz of water. Whoops! So I compensated today by not only drinking the water but also doing the plank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Years of Blogging</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/9-years-of-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 21:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/9-years-of-blogging/</guid>
      <description>Okay, I know that probably isn&amp;rsquo;t a lot compared to other bloggers out there but to me, that&amp;rsquo;s mind blowing. 9 years is around 40% of my life and that percentage will only keep on increasing. Assuming that I continue blogging. As long as I can type, I don&amp;rsquo;t think I would stop blogging. Sure, my blogging might be extremely sporadic but it&amp;rsquo;s still blogging to me.
Actually, I was going through my archive and I read a blog post that was from exactly six years and two days ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 4</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 06:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 4: Lower Body The little preamble for today in the calendar simply said to drink a glass of 8 oz of water. I have no idea what 8 oz looks like. Or how much any other measurements of liquids look like for that matter. So I just drank a regular glass of water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 3</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 06:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-3/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 3: Total Body Today&amp;rsquo;s workout starts off with 10 burpees. I will admit, I haven&amp;rsquo;t done burpees since junior high school and I totally forgot how to do them. Unlike yesterday with the sit-ups, I didn&amp;rsquo;t know how to do them at all. Like I had no notion of what a burpee was.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comics Aren’t Just Kids Stuff!</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/comics-arent-just-kids-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 01:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/comics-arent-just-kids-stuff/</guid>
      <description>I initially started writing this post in 2012. I&amp;rsquo;ve been going through and cleaning out my drafts and decided this one was worthy of continuing and actually publishing.
Comics are usually written off as being childish or something only nerds can enjoy. But, I&amp;rsquo;m not here to argue whether comics are legitimate literature or not. I&amp;rsquo;m here to point out some of my favourite web comics. I don&amp;rsquo;t know where it started but I got bored one day and eventually ended up on a web comics site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 2</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 2: Abs Today&amp;rsquo;s workout is split into two videos. Both target your abs however they vary in difficulty. It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that spot reduction (focusing on working out a specific part of your body to lose fat in that one specific area) is a myth. It&amp;rsquo;s only when your overall body fat percentage lowers that will you see results and they will be present around your whole body and not in just one area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 07:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.
My first post of 2016! This year I resolved to get healthier. That is, eat healthier and be more active! I&amp;rsquo;ve been hanging out on the /r/xxfitness: Fitness for Women subreddit a lot lately. Since I&amp;rsquo;m hesitant to go to the gym, someone suggested I try Blogilates, ran by Cassey Ho. I browsed the site a bit and decided to try the Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Workout Calendar which lasts for four weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>