<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Knitting on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/knitting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Knitting on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 13:35:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/knitting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m a Little Behind</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/im-a-little-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/im-a-little-behind/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days ago I was behind on my granny squares for my temperature blanket. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know, temperature blankets consist of one square a day and each square represents the temperature of that day. Thankfully, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to catch up with temperature blankets! Even though I&amp;rsquo;m caught up with the squares, I still haven&amp;rsquo;t woven the ends in yet nor have I joined them. Eek!
Last week I was babysitting my little cousin and he was playing with my yarn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STASH Lounge Moving and Other Outings</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/stash-lounge-moving-and-other-outings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 03:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/stash-lounge-moving-and-other-outings/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday Yesterday opened up at their new location across the street. I dragged my brother along with me to the opening.
It was absolutely lovely! They had a DJ play some music in the background, a coffee bar, and a table of yummy sweets in the back. They even had door prizes, which I suspect I didn&amp;rsquo;t win anything from but that&amp;rsquo;s totally okay.
In terms of the space, it&amp;rsquo;s great!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knitting Haul #1: LIHAO and Takumi Bamboo Needles</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/knitting/knitting-haul-1-lihao-and-takumi-bamboo-needles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/knitting/knitting-haul-1-lihao-and-takumi-bamboo-needles/</guid>
      <description>I am just starting to get into knitting as well and I decided to buy a relatively cheap set of bamboo knitting needles. I found this LIHAO Bamboo set on Amazon for around $16.99 CAD. Included are 18 pairs of needles ranging from 2.0mm to 10.0mm. It also came with a knitting gauge which is super helpful!
From a quick look over, there are no obvious defects. The reviews say that they are perfect for beginners so we&amp;rsquo;ll see!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kits and Knits</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/kits-and-knits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 22:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/kits-and-knits/</guid>
      <description>Last week was the end of final exams and on my last exam, I decided to take a well deserved day out. In celebration of Canada Day, Tim Hortons was bringing back Roll Up the Rim for a time. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to cut down on my coffee but I decided to get at least one cup, just to try my luck. Turns out that my luck isn&amp;rsquo;t that so great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yarn Haul #8: Gina Brown’s First Visit</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-8-gina-browns-first-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-8-gina-browns-first-visit/</guid>
      <description>I went to visit another local yarn store called Gina Brown&amp;rsquo;s. I was in the area waiting to meet up with some friends and decided to pop in and check the place out. It&amp;rsquo;s way too convenient that this place is a ten minute walk away from a train station.
It&amp;rsquo;s a nice store. In the back there&amp;rsquo;s a big table available for classes and (I&amp;rsquo;m assuming) to just knit or crochet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yarn Haul #7: The Knitting Room First Visit</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-7-the-knitting-room-first-visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 07:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/crochet/yarn-haul-7-the-knitting-room-first-visit/</guid>
      <description>I have been going to the Brentwood Village Mall for the past couple of years now and I have never ever noticed this nice little yarn store before until I started up crochet. The Knitting Room is a small store located in a mall close to my university. I usually go to the mall when I&amp;rsquo;m itching to walk somewhere between classes. I decided to finally visit The Knitting Room for the first time and came away with some yarn!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning How to Knit at STASH Needle Art Lounge #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/knitting/learning-how-to-knit-at-stash-needle-art-lounge-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 07:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/knitting/learning-how-to-knit-at-stash-needle-art-lounge-1/</guid>
      <description>Since I recently took up crochet, I have also been itching to start learning how to knit as well. I figure it would be advantageous to take up both of the more well known fiber art hobbies. So I signed up for lessons at one of my local yarn stores.
The store itself is very cozy and quaint. It&amp;rsquo;s literally a small house filled to the brim with yarn. The people at the front desk are extremely nice and while I was waiting for class to start, they offered me some tea.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>