<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on edel grace altares</title>
    <link>http://edelgrace.me/categories/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on edel grace altares</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://edelgrace.me/categories/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Uber Frugal Month January 2018: Day 1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/uber-frugal-month-january-2018-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/uber-frugal-month-january-2018-day-1/</guid>
      <description>This is a month-long challenge held over at Frugalwoods. Feel free to join whenever you can!
Today&amp;rsquo;s Mantra: Anything in life that’s worth doing takes effort.
Today&amp;rsquo;s Action: Write down why you’re participating in the Uber and answers to
The Homework Step 1: Establish your goals Why are you participating in this challenge?
I want to build good spending habits for when I move out. I currently still live with my parents and admittedly am still quite spoiled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 2017</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/my-2017/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR/Highlights
I didn&amp;rsquo;t accomplish as much as I would have liked this year. However, this year was extremely eventful.
 Finished my internship and saved a lot of #MovingOut money Started and finished self-esteem group therapy Went to my first hackathon at Hack the North in Waterloo, Ontario Attended both the Calgary Expo and Calgary Expo Holiday Market Was a little more social this year Ate a lot of good food (AKA went to a ton of restaurants and pubs) Started crocheting and knitting  It&amp;rsquo;s been a wild year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forever Tinkering with My Productivity System</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/forever-tinkering-with-my-productivity-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2017 23:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/forever-tinkering-with-my-productivity-system/</guid>
      <description>I follow the blog baty.net in which Jack Baty continuously finds new tools and new ways to improve his productivity. While I usually scoff at people who are always changing things up, I will admit that I am the exact same way. It would be great to just stick to something tried and true and never have to think about changing but there is just so much out there that it&amp;rsquo;s hard for me to resist the temptation to not try everything I can see.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I’m a Little Behind</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/im-a-little-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 13:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/im-a-little-behind/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days ago I was behind on my granny squares for my temperature blanket. If you don&amp;rsquo;t know, temperature blankets consist of one square a day and each square represents the temperature of that day. Thankfully, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to catch up with temperature blankets! Even though I&amp;rsquo;m caught up with the squares, I still haven&amp;rsquo;t woven the ends in yet nor have I joined them. Eek!
Last week I was babysitting my little cousin and he was playing with my yarn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STASH Lounge Moving and Other Outings</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/stash-lounge-moving-and-other-outings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 03:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/stash-lounge-moving-and-other-outings/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday Yesterday opened up at their new location across the street. I dragged my brother along with me to the opening.
It was absolutely lovely! They had a DJ play some music in the background, a coffee bar, and a table of yummy sweets in the back. They even had door prizes, which I suspect I didn&amp;rsquo;t win anything from but that&amp;rsquo;s totally okay.
In terms of the space, it&amp;rsquo;s great!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Time Crocheting on a Road Trip</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/first-time-crocheting-on-a-road-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 15:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/first-time-crocheting-on-a-road-trip/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I went to Drumheller with the family. Up to this point I haven&amp;rsquo;t had a chance to go on a long road trip with my crochet. I started this ripple afghan a couple of days ago with Bernat Blanket Stripes yarn. This blanket is intended for my cousins&amp;rsquo;s newborn son. I guess he isn&amp;rsquo;t quite so newborn now but every baby could use a blanket regardless! I actually restarted this blanket once or twice but I finally got the hang of it while on this trip.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stampede Food</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/stampede-food/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/stampede-food/</guid>
      <description>Honestly, Stampede is synonymous with food for me. Stampede means free breakfasts for a week. Usually these breakfasts consists of pancakes and sausages. We ended up going to six of these breakfasts. Some of them were worth it, some of them weren&amp;rsquo;t. One of them actually ended up being $250 because my brother got fined for forgetting to validate his train ticket on the way to a breakfast. But still, a lot of pancakey goodness!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day Out in Pre-Stampede Rush</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/day-out-in-pre-stampede-rush/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/day-out-in-pre-stampede-rush/</guid>
      <description>I went to the first pancake breakfast of the season with my family the other day. It was close to home which was a great bonus because my dad had the car for work. The breakfast wasn&amp;rsquo;t busy at all but maybe being fairly early was a factor. They only served pancakes and sausage patties but they were pretty good! There was also a Tim Hortons truck giving out free coffee and hot chocolate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kits and Knits</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/kits-and-knits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 22:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/kits-and-knits/</guid>
      <description>Last week was the end of final exams and on my last exam, I decided to take a well deserved day out. In celebration of Canada Day, Tim Hortons was bringing back Roll Up the Rim for a time. I&amp;rsquo;m trying to cut down on my coffee but I decided to get at least one cup, just to try my luck. Turns out that my luck isn&amp;rsquo;t that so great.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>25 Before 25: Update #1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/25-before-25-update-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 01:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/25-before-25-update-1/</guid>
      <description>I took a little break during the month of May. My mental health was honestly at an all time low and I found myself having a hard time picking myself back up to get motivated to actually do things. Since I am around 6 months into my 22nd year of living, I thought it would be a good time to pause and reflect how I&amp;rsquo;m doing with my 25 before 25.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Blogger Hop #16</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/book-blogger-hop-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Apr 2017 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/book-blogger-hop-16/</guid>
      <description>Book Blogger Hop is a weekly meme run by Coffee Addicted Writer. Every Friday, a question is posted for the book blog community to discuss. This week&amp;rsquo;s question is&amp;#8230;
 Would you stop reading a book if an element of the plot strongly clashed with your personal beliefs, or would you continue reading until you finished the book?
 I would definitely finish the book. At least, that&amp;rsquo;s what I think and hope I would do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Hour at Cafe Blanca</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/an-hour-at-cafe-blanca/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2017 09:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/an-hour-at-cafe-blanca/</guid>
      <description>There&amp;rsquo;s a cool hip place at the edge of Calgary&amp;rsquo;s Chinatown and across Eau Claire Market called Cafe Blanca. They&amp;rsquo;re most known for their Siphon coffee which I unfortunately did not remember to try. Instead, I ordered a plain normal latte and a cheesecake.

Now, I&amp;rsquo;m not cheesecake expert but I&amp;rsquo;m definitely a cheesecake lover. I got myself a mint chocolate cheesecake. It was extremely delicious. It was a little more cake than I prefer (the base was an actual chocolate cake and yes, cake, not brownie) and not as much cheese as I&amp;rsquo;d like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paint Nite Calgary at Yuk Yuk’s Comedy Club</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/paint-nite-at-yuk-yuks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2017 07:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/paint-nite-at-yuk-yuks/</guid>
      <description>One of the interns at my workplace suggested going painting as an activity that we could all do together. It seemed fun so we decided to give it a try! Paint Nite is a series of painting events held at bars, each session hosted by different people.
That day we went to Yuk Yuk&amp;rsquo;s Comedy Club which is a few minutes walk from Victoria Park Stampede. We were really confused about the food since there was no (or incorrect) information on the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art, Food, and Good Old Bowling</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/art-food-and-good-old-bowling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 09:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/art-food-and-good-old-bowling/</guid>
      <description>At the company where I&amp;rsquo;m doing an internship right now offered all the interns the opportunity to go to their downtown location and give us a tour of all the art. It seems a little weird to give art tours in an office environment but once we stepped into the building, it made sense. There was art on every single floor of the building (of which there are over ten floors) and almost every single wall has a piece of art hanging on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Can I Get Coffee After Five in this City?</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/where-can-i-get-coffee-after-five-in-this-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 05:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/where-can-i-get-coffee-after-five-in-this-city/</guid>
      <description>I found myself in downtown with cancelled plans the other day. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to be home for another two hours so I decided to try a new coffee place. It was around five in the evening. I pulled up Google Maps and searched for coffee.
Scrolling through the list, I found that most of the coffee places closed at 5:00PM or 6:00PM. I needed a place to sit and blog hop for a little bit so that was no good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Joined a Gym</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/i-joined-a-gym/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/i-joined-a-gym/</guid>
      <description>In an attempt to do more things in my free time, I decided to join a gym. My original plan was to go to my university gym however since I am on co-op, I no longer have the discounted membership included in my tuition. Instead, I opted for my local Fit4Less. It is an extremely more convenient location, significantly cheaper, and a good &amp;ldquo;introductory&amp;rdquo; gym for those who are just starting out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Drawing #3</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/weekly-drawing-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 02:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/blog/life/weekly-drawing-3/</guid>
      <description>Last week&amp;rsquo;s theme was fantasy. The original picture was a lot more ethereal and pretty. I had to redraw this one because I messed up the background. The background was definitely the hardest part because the original picture relied heavily on colour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cookie Icing Charades</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/cookie-icing-charades/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 06:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/cookie-icing-charades/</guid>
      <description>The Game
Take turns to ice an object or living being onto a cookie. Everyone guesses what that person iced onto the cookie. There are no winners, just a bunch of people having fun and joking around about their lack of (or possession of) artistic ability.
The Background
Over the holidays I was baking brownies and cookies with my cousins. The brownies had left over frosting so we decided to ice the cookies with cool designs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back to Work…</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/back-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 03:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/back-to-work/</guid>
      <description>The holidays are officially over, for I went back to work today. It was a bit of a slow day. I got my internship extended, however they basically treated me as a new hire since my contract ended in December. So I&amp;rsquo;m starting from scratch, essentially. I had no laptop, no e-mail, no account to login into any computer connected to the company&amp;rsquo;s network&amp;#8230; Kinda rough.
However, I did manage to do some small tasks that didn&amp;rsquo;t require the use of a computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>25 Before 25</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/25-before-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 19:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/25-before-25/</guid>
      <description>New Years Resolutions are no longer the in thing. I recently turned 22 and it feels like my life is whizzing by now. I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about my goals but there are just too many that I have for one year and a couple that will go beyond 2017. So I figured a 25 before 25 would be appropriate.
1. Graduate from university
I&amp;rsquo;ve been in university since I was 17.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Week, New Me</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/new-week-new-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 04:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/new-week-new-me/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I had eaten two plates piled high with sweet American-Chinese prepared meats, a plate full of sweet desserts, and a take-out box of homemade cookies. On Friday I almost consumed an entire bag of buttery popcorn but the bag spilled into the aisle as it descended up the movie theatre steps. As I heard the small popped kernels tumble out of the bag, I felt both relief and disappointment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 28</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 19:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-28/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 28: Rest Day Oh my goodness, today is the last day of the fitness calendar! I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I made it! I didn&amp;rsquo;t make this cookie (I haven&amp;rsquo;t made any of the rest day recipes) but like with the rest of the recipes, I would love to try this eventually!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 27</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 04:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-27/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 27: Total Body Today is the last day of the beginner&amp;rsquo;s workout calendar, not including the rest day tomorrow! I think I&amp;rsquo;ll make a blog post the day after rest day to talk about how the month went. As for today, today was a lot of sweat and groaning! A lot of cardio today, even if it isn&amp;rsquo;t intensive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 26</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 05:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-26/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 26: Abs Video 1: Train Insane HIIT Workout  Video 2: Muffintop Shredder Workout I can&amp;rsquo;t remember anymore but I think I&amp;rsquo;ve done this video before. This video is really simple, there is just one move: the candlestick. I think I was doing it properly this time because I started to get tired and I could feel burning in my limbs and my core (I can&amp;rsquo;t be as technical as Cassey, what are my obliques?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 25</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 06:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-25/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 25: Lower Body Video 1: Far Burning Cardio Warmup I&amp;rsquo;ve done this video so many times that I&amp;rsquo;ve almost memorized everything Cassey said, haha! The moves in this video are easy and fun, as always.
 Video 2: Hips Butt &amp;#8216;n Thighs Super Shaper Workout   Hot Potato: This is a nice and easy move to start off the video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 24</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 05:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-24/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 24: Lower Body I&amp;rsquo;m still behind&amp;#8230; Oh well, I mostly caught up today. I still have one video to do for day 25 but it&amp;rsquo;s day 25 now and I have three hours left to do it! Today was pretty hard but that could be due to the fact I did two days in one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 23</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2016 07:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-23/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 23: Abs Okay I&amp;rsquo;m pretty behind. It&amp;rsquo;s now past midnight, I should be doing day 25 today. I&amp;rsquo;m waking up early tomorrow so I&amp;rsquo;ll have to skip out on catching up on day 24 until later in the day. Yesterday (two days ago?) I came home late with a huge head ache and immediately fell asleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 22</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2016 07:12:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-22/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 22: Total Body I was so close to not doing today&amp;rsquo;s workout because I came home late from a volunteering gig with a raging head ache. I slept for about four hours and woke up around 10:30. It took me a while to get started with the workout, I didn&amp;rsquo;t start until 11:15 and I finished at 11:55!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 21</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 06:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-21/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 21: Rest Day Today was a much needed rest day. Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been having the tendency to fall asleep as soon as I get home, which sucks. So I decided to just sleep, haha! I didn&amp;rsquo;t try out the pizza. Maybe one day. Seriously, one day I will try all of her recipes!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 20</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 05:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-20/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 19: Total Body I got home today after writing a midterm and I was so tired that I was tempted to just not do the workout today but then I realized tomorrow os rest day and who wants to work out on rest day? Not me. So I decided against it and got off my butt to do it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 19</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 02:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-19/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 19: Abs I loathe ab days. They&amp;rsquo;re really hard and not that fun, haha. But I really do feel the burn the most on these days. I need to work on this&amp;#8230;
Video 1: Fun Indoor Cardio Workout There are A LOT of kicks in this video. I did my workout in the morning today so I had to do some modifications, as always.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 18</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 06:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-18/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 18: Lower Body Because I had to make up day 17 today, I broke the two workouts up throughout the day. But near the end of the day, I just did the last two videos all at once. This day&amp;rsquo;s workout is surprisingly not that bad. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have any trouble with the moves today which was&amp;#8230; Weird but satisfying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 17</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2016 04:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-17/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 17: Total Body Okay, this is the first time I have skipped a day and had to make it up. I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel too guilty about skipping yesterday because I had spin class, which is two (maybe even three) times as long and 234204398 times harder than these workouts. I enjoy spin class though, don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 16</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 06:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-16/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 16: Abs Okay, this is the first day that I technically did not do on the right day. I started this one a little after midnight because I was working on an assignment and then I looked at the time&amp;#8230; Whoops, the day went by fast! Today&amp;rsquo;s videos were okay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 15</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 06:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-15/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 15: Total Body My body issues seem to have improved, minus the random headaches. I tried my best to stay active and not give into my pain. I might have to go to the doctor tomorrow though, if it gets any worse. Both videos today contained moves that were not named so I&amp;rsquo;m not going to bother with going through each move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 14</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 04:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-14/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 14: Rest Day Ummm, what?? It&amp;rsquo;s rest day already?? I do not believe it. I&amp;rsquo;ve been at this for two weeks now! I feel proud of myself, I never thought I would be able to make it this far. I&amp;rsquo;m officially halfway through the calendar! I decided not to do a workout video today because I&amp;rsquo;ve been so tired and lethargic lately and all of my limbs feel sore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 13</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 06:47:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-13/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 13: Total Body Video 1: 5 Minute Fat Burner &amp;ldquo;Five minutes? Easy peasey.&amp;rdquo; I was so wrong! Cassey wasn&amp;rsquo;t lying when she said it would be tough. This was a hard video, with lots of suffering included (guaranteed).
  Star Jump: These were really hard to do quietly. I definitely started sweating immediately with this move.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 12</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Feb 2016 03:14:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-12/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 12: Abs Ab workouts are so brutal&amp;#8230; And, of course, that&amp;rsquo;s what everyone wants to workout. Cue the suffering.
Video 1: Ab &amp;amp; Butt Workout I seriously cannot get over how cute Rosanna is! She is absolutely adorable and when she struggles, I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m not alone in ab hell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 11</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 14:20:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-11/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 11: Lower Body Another day, another week almost finished (I&amp;rsquo;m talking in terms of the weekday week and not the Blogilates week)! I keep mixing up the &amp;ldquo;Wake up and &amp;#8230;&amp;rdquo; preambles at the start of each day&amp;#8230;. Yesterday I did 30 second planks on each side instead of just 1 minute of planking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 10</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calenday-2-0-day-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 06:59:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calenday-2-0-day-10/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 10: Abs The day starts off with two thirty second planks on each side. How I hate planks&amp;#8230; But I did it anyway, even if I cheated for a couple seconds on each. There&amp;rsquo;s only one new video today and I decided that I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t list all the moves for the other videos again in the interest of time and because I don&amp;rsquo;t really have anything to say about specific moves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 9</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 06:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-9/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 9: Abs Video 1: Total Body Workout I&amp;rsquo;m not going to list the moves for this video again because my comments are mostly the same from the last time I did this video. I really am progressing with those pull ups. Not once did I have to grab my legs!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 8</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 06:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-8/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 8: Total Body After my &amp;ldquo;rest day&amp;rdquo; I&amp;rsquo;ve been missing Cassey a little. It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe that it&amp;rsquo;s already the second week! It doesn&amp;rsquo;t feel like it&amp;rsquo;s been that long&amp;#8230;
Video 1: Indoor Cardio Workout I wish I had more time to do workouts in the morning because when it comes to the cardio videos, I just can&amp;rsquo;t do them 100% without making a bunch of noise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 7</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 06:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-7/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 7: Rest Day Thank goodness for the rest day. Technically there is 30 minutes left of day 7 and I feel like I should be doing something. So I&amp;rsquo;m searching for some quick videos to do before midnight hits. I can&amp;rsquo;t believe I&amp;rsquo;ve done a week of this already! Here&amp;rsquo;s to four more weeks!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 6</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 01:45:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-6/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 6: Total Body &amp;ldquo;Wake up and do 15 crunches.&amp;rdquo; I did four roll ups instead. And I never do these when I wake up, usually it&amp;rsquo;s the last thing I do before bed. Not today though!
Video 1: Cardio Warmup I&amp;rsquo;m really glad Cassey puts some cardio videos because most of her workouts are focusing on toning and my main goal is to burn fat and not really &amp;ldquo;bulk&amp;rdquo; up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 5</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 07:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-5/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 5: Abs Okay I switched up the preambles in the calendar because apparently I can&amp;rsquo;t read. Day three I was supposed to plank for 30 seconds, yesterday I was supposed to do the burpees, and today I was supposed to drink an 8 oz of water. Whoops! So I compensated today by not only drinking the water but also doing the plank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Years of Blogging</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/9-years-of-blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 21:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/9-years-of-blogging/</guid>
      <description>Okay, I know that probably isn&amp;rsquo;t a lot compared to other bloggers out there but to me, that&amp;rsquo;s mind blowing. 9 years is around 40% of my life and that percentage will only keep on increasing. Assuming that I continue blogging. As long as I can type, I don&amp;rsquo;t think I would stop blogging. Sure, my blogging might be extremely sporadic but it&amp;rsquo;s still blogging to me.
Actually, I was going through my archive and I read a blog post that was from exactly six years and two days ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 4</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2016 06:42:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-4/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 4: Lower Body The little preamble for today in the calendar simply said to drink a glass of 8 oz of water. I have no idea what 8 oz looks like. Or how much any other measurements of liquids look like for that matter. So I just drank a regular glass of water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 2</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-2/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.

Day 2: Abs Today&amp;rsquo;s workout is split into two videos. Both target your abs however they vary in difficulty. It&amp;rsquo;s worth noting that spot reduction (focusing on working out a specific part of your body to lose fat in that one specific area) is a myth. It&amp;rsquo;s only when your overall body fat percentage lowers that will you see results and they will be present around your whole body and not in just one area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogilates Beginner’s Workout Calendar 2.0: Day 1</title>
      <link>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 07:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edelgrace.me/life/blogilates-beginners-workout-calendar-2-0-day-1/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: This &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo;/blog series is NOT sponsored in any way and all opinions are entirely of my own.
My first post of 2016! This year I resolved to get healthier. That is, eat healthier and be more active! I&amp;rsquo;ve been hanging out on the /r/xxfitness: Fitness for Women subreddit a lot lately. Since I&amp;rsquo;m hesitant to go to the gym, someone suggested I try Blogilates, ran by Cassey Ho. I browsed the site a bit and decided to try the Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Workout Calendar which lasts for four weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>